<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Packages xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Package>
		<id>1</id>
		<Name>STB Special Tours</Name>
		<Duration>7</Duration>
		<Place1>underwater world</Place1>
		<Place2>Dolphin Lagoon</Place2>
		<Place3>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place3>
		<Place4>Tiger Sky Tower</Place4>
		<Place5>cable car-sentosa</Place5>
		<Place6>CHIJMES</Place6>
		<Place7>Feng Shui tour</Place7>
		<Place8>Night Safari</Place8>
    		<Place9>World's largest Fountain</Place9>
    		<Place10>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place10>
		<Place11>Chinatown Night Market</Place11>
		<Place12>Trishaw</Place12>
		<Place13>Clarke Quay</Place13>
		<Place14>Bumboat River</Place14>
		<Place15>shopping little india</Place15>
		<Place16>Shopping Orchard</Place16>
		<Place17>Duck Tour</Place17>
		<Place18>Singapore Zoo</Place18>
		<Place19>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place19>
		<Place20>Zouk</Place20>
		<Place21>Clarke Quay</Place21>
		<Place22>A Kampong Glam Walk</Place22>
		<Place23>geylang serai</Place23>
		<Place24>Sultan Mosque</Place24>
		<Place25>Arab Street</Place25>
		<Place26>Parliament House</Place26>
		<Place27>supreme court and city hall</Place27>
		<Place28>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place28>
		<Place29>Bumboat river</Place29>
		<Place30>Jurong Bird Park</Place30>
		<Place31>esplanade</Place31>
		<Place32>Fish Reflexology</Place32>
		<Place33>Lau Pa Sat</Place33>
		<Place34>Katong antique house</Place34>
		<Place35>Katong-Joo chiat</Place35>
		<Place36>Peranakan museum</Place36>
		<Description>DAY 1
Your first Singapore morning could see you marvelling at a tropical sunrise followed by a leisurely breakfast on the sandy beaches of Sentosa Island. After breakfast, enjoy all that this exciting island has to offer. Take your pick from cycling and rollerblading or visit attractions such as the Underwater World, Dolphin Lagoon, Butterfly Park, Insect Kingdom and the Carlsberg Sky Tower before returning to the mainland via cable car.
Once back, it's time to stop for a relaxing lunch at the historic CHIJMES, where you can take your pick from any of the restaurants and pubs in this restored 19th century convent. After that, embark on the Feng Shui tour and learn all about the ancient Chinese practice of harnessing the
powers of nature to promote wealth and health. Scale one of the tallest buildings in Singapore and find out how feng shui played a part in shaping its design. As you marvel at the world’s largest fountain at Suntec City, listen to the tales of people who discovered success after their faithful visits
to the fountain.
For a night of excitement and adventure, visit the Night Safari. Keep your eyes peeled for elusive nocturnal creatures
as you journey slowly through their natural habitats aboard a tram. Wander off and explore the well-lit trails on foot
for a closer encounter before wrapping up the evening with an exotic meal at one of the jungle-themed restaurants.
DAY 2
Share a hearty breakfast of kaya (egg and coconut jam) on toast before taking in the cultural treats of Chinatown and Little India. Take your pick of ethnic souvenirs and local
handicrafts including saris, batik, art and handmade jewellery, as you discover the colours of the mystical East.
Feeling hungry? Indulge in a piquant curry cooked with famous Eastern spices and served on a banana leaf. Walk off the hearty lunch with a shopping expedition along the
famed Orchard Road, the mecca of shoppers seeking international brands, electrical devices and designer fashion.
As the sun sets, take in a tantalising dinner at the lavish One Fullerton before partying the night away at the worldfamous Zouk or at one of the many pubs and clubs along
the exuberant Mohamed Sultan Road.
DAY 3
Fancy something wild for breakfast? You are invited to come
and dine in the company of some of nature’s most amazing
creatures at the Singapore Zoo. This widely-acclaimed,
modern open zoo will leave you mesmerised, as you get
up close with amazing animals from all corners of the globe.
Following your stroll of this hugely popular zoo, you can
trace the footsteps of early British settlers at the lush
Singapore Botanic Gardens.
For lunch, treat yourself to a perfectly balanced meal at the
famed Imperial Herbal Restaurant, where you’ll savour dishes
that soothe the mind as well as satisfy the body. After lunch,
hitch a wild ride on the amphibious half-boat, half-truck
craft from Singapore DuckTours and journey through the
Civic District before splashing into the Singapore River. Get
acquainted with all the stately architecture, monuments and
sculptures, and you’ll soon discover why Singapore is home
to a lively and diverse arts scene that attracts artists from
all walks of life.
As dusk approaches, visit Clarke Quay for a night of riverside
entertainment. Jump onto a quaint bumboat as it meanders
its way along the enchanting Singapore River, taking in popular sights such as the Asian Civilisations Museum at
Empress Place, the Merlion and the Esplanade – Theatres
on the Bay. Once back on land, sample local favourites at
the renowned Satay Club before soaking up the atmosphere
at one of the many trendy riverside pubs or watering holes.
DAY 4
Start the morning with a tasty breakfast of roti-prata
(a South Indian crispy, crusty pancake served with curry
gravy) before discovering life in old Singapore decades past
with the Heartlands of Singapore tour. The hustle and bustle
of the city will give way to the quiet atmosphere of Malay
Village on the eastern part of Singapore, where you get
glimpses of kampung (Malay village) lifestyle in the 1950s
and 60s. Afterwards you’ll be taken to the Changi Chapel and Museum, with its replica of a typical World War II chapel before journeying through a typical modern housing estate.
In the afternoon, it’s time to join our feathered friends at the Jurong BirdPark – home to over 9,000 birds. Make sure you catch the colourful Parrot Paradise, the breathtaking simulated thunderstorm and the live bird shows. 
Come nightfall, make your way to the new performing arts venue, Esplanade – Theatres on the Bay, for an evening of world-class performances. Afterwards, dine in the company of stars at one of the harbour-front alfresco cafes.
DAY 5
Prepare your mind, body and spirit for the day ahead with a relaxing foot reflexology session before making your way to Eu Yan Sang, one of the island’s oldest medicine halls, to
sample some traditional Chinese medicine.
Enjoy a traditional lunch at the quaint Lau Pa Sat, one of Singapore’s most colourful hawker centres, before exploring
the historic Peranakan Place and Emerald Hill where traditional shophouses built in true Peranakan (of mixed
Chinese and Malay ancestry) style still stand.
In the evening, immerse yourself in the colonial splendour of the opulent Raffles Hotel as you relax with the famous
Singapore Sling under the evening sky. The numerous restaurants at the hotel each have their own amazing legends
and are the perfect place to reward well-earned appetites.
As you will discover, your adventures in Singapore will leave you with a renewed vigour, not to mention, a few tales to tell. So come and experience all that this island paradise has to offer..</Description>
		<references>Singapore Travel Agent Book</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>2</id>
		<Name>Culinary Heritage Tour</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>foodwalk-spicy-food</Place1>
		<Place2>Cricket club</Place2>
		<Place3>Parliament House</Place3>
		<Place4>Supreme court and city Hall</Place4>
		<Place5>Merlion park</Place5>
		<Place6>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place6>
		<Place7>Handicraft centre</Place7>
		<Place8>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place8>
		<Place9>Chinatown Night Market</Place9>
		<Place10>Trishaw</Place10>
		<Place11>Clarke Quay</Place11>
		<Place12>Bumboat River</Place12>
		<Place13>Shopping Little India</Place13>
		<Place14>geylang serai</Place14>
		<Description>The ultimate "Eat Your Heart Out Holiday" tour. 
This five-day package brings you on a gastronomic journey of famous Singapore foods. A local food celebrity (optional) will share her knowledge about the distinctive features of Singapore’s key ethnic cuisine, from Malay and Chinese to Indian and
Peranakan.</Description>
		<references>Singapore Travel Agent Book</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>3</id>
		<Name>Honeymoon in Singapore</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place2>
		<Place3>Chinatown Night Market</Place3>
		<Place4>Trishaw</Place4>
		<Place5>Clarke Quay</Place5>
		<Place6>Bumboat River</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Gem Stone Factory</Place8>
		<Place9>The DHL Balloon</Place9>
		<Place10>cable car-sentosa</Place10>
		<Place11>Underwater World</Place11>
		<Place12>Merlion</Place12>
		<Place13>Causeway Bridge</Place13>
		<Place14>Night Safari</Place14>
		<Description>After breakfast, take a half day tour of Singapore City Covering Merlion, Chinatown, Mount Faber And Gem Stone Factory on Hippo Bus. The open top double decker bus can offer you the advantage at a 360 - degree, uniterrupted panoramic view of city showcasing the best of Singapore with 22 strategic stops, during the city tour a DHL Balloon Ride would be arranged for you,enjoy the breathtaking view of city in it. Singapore's latest theme ttraction! At 6500 cubic metres,DHL Balloon is the world's Largest Tethered Helium Balloon. Overnight at the hotel 
3. After breakfast, Visit the famous Sentosa Island and Night Safari as per your Choices.Overnight at hotel.</Description>
		<references>http://www.joy-travels.com/outbound.asp?p=4%20Days/3%20Nights%20Honeymoon%20in%20Singapore</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>4</id>
		<Name>Pure Singapore 1</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place2>
		<Place3>Chinatown Night Market</Place3>
		<Place4>Trishaw</Place4>
		<Place5>Clarke Quay</Place5>
		<Place6>Bumboat River</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Gem Stone Factory</Place8>
		<Place9>Cricket club</Place9>
		<Place10>Parliament House</Place10>
		<Place11>Supreme court and city Hall</Place11>
		<Place12>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place12>
		<Place13>Handicraft centre</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird park</Place14>
		<Place15>cable car-sentosa</Place15>
		<Place16>Underwater World</Place16>
		<Place17>Merlion</Place17>
		<Place18>Causeway Bridge</Place18>
		<Description>Arrive at the fabulous Changi Airport in Singapore. Our local representative will be waiting outside the customs area to welcome and take you to your hotel. Day free to relax. Overnight at hotel. After breakfast, take a half day tour of Singapore City covering Merlion, Chinatown, Mount Faber And Gem stone factory. Overnight at the hotel.</Description>
		<references>http://www.joy-travels.com/outbound.asp?p=Pure%20Singapore</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>5</id>
		<Name>Pure Singapore 2</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place2>
		<Place3>Chinatown Night Market</Place3>
		<Place4>Trishaw</Place4>
		<Place5>Clarke Quay</Place5>
		<Place6>Bumboat River</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Gem Stone Factory</Place8>
		<Place9>Cricket club</Place9>
		<Place10>Parliament House</Place10>
		<Place11>Supreme court and city Hall</Place11>
		<Place12>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place12>
		<Place13>Handicraft centre</Place13>
		<Place14>cable car-sentosa</Place14>
		<Place15>Underwater World</Place15>
		<Place16>Merlion</Place16>
		<Place17>Causeway Bridge</Place17>
		<Place18>Night Safari</Place18>
		<Description>Arrive at the fabulous Changi Airport in Singapore. Our local representative will be waiting outside the customs area to welcome and take you to your hotel. Day free to relax. Overnight at hotel. After breakfast, take a half day tour of Singapore City covering Merlion, Chinatown, Mount Faber And Gem stone factory. Overnight at the hotel.</Description>
		<references>http://www.joy-travels.com/outbound.asp?p=Pure%20Singapore</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>6</id>
		<Name>Pure Singapore 3</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place2>
		<Place3>Chinatown Night Market</Place3>
		<Place4>Trishaw</Place4>
		<Place5>Clarke Quay</Place5>
		<Place6>Bumboat River</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Gem Stone Factory</Place8>
		<Place9>Cricket club</Place9>
		<Place10>Parliament House</Place10>
		<Place11>Supreme court and city Hall</Place11>
		<Place12>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place12>
		<Place13>Handicraft centre</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird park</Place14>
		<Place15>Singapore Zoo</Place15>
		<Description>Arrive at the fabulous Changi Airport in Singapore. Our local representative will be waiting outside the customs area to welcome and take you to your hotel. Day free to relax. Overnight at hotel. After breakfast, take a half day tour of Singapore City covering Merlion, Chinatown, Mount Faber And Gem stone factory. Overnight at the hotel.</Description>
		<references>http://www.joy-travels.com/outbound.asp?p=Pure%20Singapore</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>7</id>
		<Name>Singapore With Star Cruise</Name>
		<Duration>6</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Night Safari</Place7>
		<Place8>Sunset at Sentosa</Place8>
		<Place9>Singapore Zoo</Place9>
		<Place10>star cruise</Place10>
		<Place11>Shopping Orchard</Place11>
		<Place12>National Orchid Garden</Place12>
		<Place13>Jurong Bird Park</Place13>
		<Description>Arrive at the fabulous Changi Airport in Singapore. Our local representative will be waiting outside the customs area to welcome and take you to your hotel. Day free to relax. Overnight at hotel. 
Day 2 :  Singapore 
After breakfast, take a half day tour of Singapore City. At night you may go for a Night Safari(optional). Overnight at the hotel 
Day 3 :  Singapore 
After breakfast,you check out of the hotel. You may like to visit the Sentosa Island(optional) or the Singapore Zoo (optional). Overnight at hotel. 
 Day 4 :  Singapore with star cruise 
After breakfast,you will board the cruise.Overnight at cruise. 
 Day 5 :  Singapore with star cruise 
Enjoy the shows and other activities on the cruise.Overnight at cruise. 
 Day 6 :  Singapore-Delhi 
After breakfast this day is free for shopping. Later. we transfer you to the Airport for your flight home.</Description>
		<references>http://www.joy-travels.com/outbound.asp?p=Singapore%20with%20star%20cruise</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>8</id>
		<Name>8 Days Singapore to Vacation</Name>
		<Duration>8</Duration>
		<Place1>Night Safari</Place1>
		<Place2>World's largest Fountain</Place2>
		<Place3>Shopping in Bugis</Place3>
		<Place4>Cricket club</Place4>
		<Place5>Parliament House</Place5>
		<Place6>Supreme court and city Hall</Place6>
		<Place7>Merlion park</Place7>
		<Place8>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place8>
		<Place9>Handicraft centre</Place9>
		<Place10>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place10>
		<Place11>Chinatown Night Market</Place11>
		<Place12>Trishaw</Place12>
		<Place13>Clarke Quay</Place13>
		<Place14>Bumboat River</Place14>
		<Place15>National Orchid Garden</Place15>
		<Place16>Little India arcade</Place16>
		<Place17>Haw Par Villa</Place17>
		<Place18>Kranji War Memorial</Place18>
		<Place19>Kong Meng San Phor Kark See Temple</Place19>
		<Description>Day 1: USA to Singapore - International flight. 
Day 2: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 3: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or take part in the optional Singapore by night with dinner and sling ($50). Take pleasure in traditional alfresco dining by the Singapore River at Boat Quay, Singaporean's latest sunset haunt. Following dinner, en route to the world's largest fountain, admire the silhouetted sight of the central business district via Benjamin Sheares Bridge. Continue to Bugis Street, as your guide takes you for a flood-lit stroll through "pasar malam," Singapore's bustling night market. Your final stop of the evening will be the Raffles Hotel for a taste of Singapore's signature concoction--"the Singapore Sling."  (B) 
Day 4: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or join the optional half day Singapore city tour ($23). This half day city tour begins with a drive through Singapore's "Colonial Heart," with views of the Padang, Cricket Club, Parliament House, Supreme Court and City Hall. Stop at the Merlion Park for splendid views and photo shots of the Marina Bay. View the stunning Thian Hock Keng Temple, Singapore's oldest temple, dedicated to the Chinese Goddess of the sea, Ma Chu P'oh. From the temple, pass by Chinatown, stopping briefly to observe local craftsmen at work. Continue to the National Orchid Garden, situated upon a large hill within the beautiful Singapore Botanic Gardens, to view a sprawling display of 60,000 variegated orchids. Proceed to Little India, where your senses will come alive with the scents of jasmine and spices. (B) 
Day 5: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or join the optional full day round island tour ($55). This full day tour offers insight outside of the city on the history and culture of Singapore, beginning with a visit to Haw Par Villa, a park created to preserve Chinese values, legends and folklore. Next, proceed to the Kranji War Memorial which was unveiled in 1957. The Memorial overlooks the Straits of Johor and serves as the final resting place for many allied soldiers who fell during World War II. It commemorates over 20,000 men and women, many of which have no known grave. Following lunch, enjoy a visit to Kong Meng San Phor Kark See Temple, or Bright Hill Temple, the largest Temple in Singapore. Built in 1920 over a hillside, the Temple is famous for its Chinese crematorium and self-sustaining turtle pond. Drive past the Johore Battery built by the British in 1939, and view a replica "Monster Gun," one of the largest guns installed outside Great Britain during World War II. The final stop is the Changi Chapel and Museum. The Museum focuses on the memories and lives of both POWs and civilian internees, and the Chapel, housed within the open-air courtyard of the Museum, is a symbolic replica of the many chapels built during the Japanese Occupation.  (B) 
Day 6: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 7: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 8: Singapore to USA 
Board your flight to travel home</Description>
		<references>http://www.tourvacationstogo.com/singapore_tours.cfm?npid=11242andnhr=1</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>9</id>
		<Name>8 daYS Thanks Giving in Singapore</Name>
		<Duration>8</Duration>
		<Place1>Night Safari</Place1>
		<Place2>World's largest Fountain</Place2>
		<Place3>Shopping in Bugis</Place3>
		<Place4>Cricket club</Place4>
		<Place5>Parliament House</Place5>
		<Place6>Supreme court and city Hall</Place6>
		<Place7>Merlion park</Place7>
		<Place8>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place8>
		<Place9>Handicraft centre</Place9>
		<Place10>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place10>
		<Place11>Chinatown Night Market</Place11>
		<Place12>Trishaw</Place12>
		<Place13>Clarke Quay</Place13>
		<Place14>Bumboat River</Place14>
		<Place15>National Orchid Garden</Place15>
		<Place16>Little India arcade</Place16>
		<Place17>Haw Par Villa</Place17>
		<Place18>Kranji War Memorial</Place18>
		<Place19>kong meng san phor kark see temple</Place19>
		<Place20>Johore Battery</Place20>
		<Place21>changi chapel and museum</Place21>
		<Description>Day 1: USA to Singapore - International flight. 
Day 2: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 3: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or take part in the optional Singapore by night with dinner and sling ($50). Take pleasure in traditional alfresco dining by the Singapore River at Boat Quay, Singaporean's latest sunset haunt. Following dinner, en route to the world's largest fountain, admire the silhouetted sight of the central business district via Benjamin Sheares Bridge. Continue to Bugis Street, as your guide takes you for a flood-lit stroll through "pasar malam," Singapore's bustling night market. Your final stop of the evening will be the Raffles Hotel for a taste of Singapore's signature concoction--"the Singapore Sling."  (B) 
Day 4: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or join the optional half day Singapore city tour ($23). This half day city tour begins with a drive through Singapore's "Colonial Heart," with views of the Padang, Cricket Club, Parliament House, Supreme Court and City Hall. Stop at the Merlion Park for splendid views and photo shots of the Marina Bay. View the stunning Thian Hock Keng Temple, Singapore's oldest temple, dedicated to the Chinese Goddess of the sea, Ma Chu P'oh. From the temple, pass by Chinatown, stopping briefly to observe local craftsmen at work. Continue to the National Orchid Garden, situated upon a large hill within the beautiful Singapore Botanic Gardens, to view a sprawling display of 60,000 variegated orchids. Proceed to Little India, where your senses will come alive with the scents of jasmine and spices. (B) 
Day 5: Singapore 
Day is at leisure or join the optional full day round island tour ($55). This full day tour offers insight outside of the city on the history and culture of Singapore, beginning with a visit to Haw Par Villa, a park created to preserve Chinese values, legends and folklore. Next, proceed to the Kranji War Memorial which was unveiled in 1957. The Memorial overlooks the Straits of Johor and serves as the final resting place for many allied soldiers who fell during World War II. It commemorates over 20,000 men and women, many of which have no known grave. Following lunch, enjoy a visit to Kong Meng San Phor Kark See Temple, or Bright Hill Temple, the largest Temple in Singapore. Built in 1920 over a hillside, the Temple is famous for its Chinese crematorium and self-sustaining turtle pond. Drive past the Johore Battery built by the British in 1939, and view a replica "Monster Gun," one of the largest guns installed outside Great Britain during World War II. The final stop is the Changi Chapel and Museum. The Museum focuses on the memories and lives of both POWs and civilian internees, and the Chapel, housed within the open-air courtyard of the Museum, is a symbolic replica of the many chapels built during the Japanese Occupation.  (B) 
Day 6: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 7: Singapore 
Day is at leisure.  (B) 
Day 8: Singapore to USA 
Board your flight to travel home</Description>
		<references>http://www.tourvacationstogo.com/singapore_tours.cfm?npid=11242andnhr=1</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>10</id>
		<Name>Singapore Experience</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>A Kampong Glam Walk</Place7>
		<Place8>geylang serai</Place8>
		<Place9>Sultan Mosque</Place9>
		<Place10>Arab Street</Place10>
		<Place11>Bumboat river</Place11>
		<Place12>Night Safari</Place12>
		<Place13>Sunset at Sentosa</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird Park</Place14>
		<Place15>Suntec City Mall</Place15>
		<Description>NULL</Description>
		<references>http://www.travelmasti.com/international/asia/singapore-holiday-packages.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>11</id>
		<Name>Singapore Flyer and Farm Visit One Day Tour</Name>
		<Duration>1</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Singapore Flyer</Place7>
		<Place8>Aero-green Technology</Place8>
		<Description>Assemble at meeting place.
Depart to City Tour, continue with Singapore Flyer Ride.
Proceed to local Restaurant for lunch
Continue journey to Farm Visit</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>12</id>
		<Name>Singapore 2days 1Night Land Package A</Name>
		<Duration>2</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>Raffles Landing Sites</Place2>
		<Place3>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place3>
		<Place4>Chinatown Night Market</Place4>
		<Place5>underwater world</Place5>
		<Place6>Butterfly_Insect_Kingdom</Place6>
		<Place7>Tiger Sky Tower</Place7>
		<Place8>Sentosa 4D Magix</Place8>
		<Place9>Bumboat River</Place9>
		<Place10>Clarke Quay</Place10>
		<Place11>Trishaw</Place11>
		<Description>Day 01 : Meet the tour guide upon arrival. Proceed to Merlion Park, Raffles Landing Site, Chinatown. After Dinner, visit 
Singapore River and Boat Ride at        Famous Night Spot ~ Clarke Quay.
Day 02 : Breakfast in Hotel. Check out hotel and proceed to Sentosa Island ~ Underwater World, Butterfly Park, Sky Tower, 
4D Magix ( Own Expense ).     End of the tour, depart to Changi International Airport.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>13</id>
		<Name>Singapore 2days 1Night Land Package B</Name>
		<Duration>2</Duration>
		<Place1>Fountain of Wealth</Place1>
		<Place2>Merlion Park</Place2>
		<Place3>Little India arcade</Place3>
		<Place4>Night Safari</Place4>
		<Place5>Images of Singapore</Place5>
		<Place6>Underwater World</Place6>
		<Place7>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place7>
		<Place8>Siloso Beach</Place8>
		<Place9>Tiger Sky Tower</Place9>
    <Place10>Causeway Bridge</Place10>
		<Place11>songs of the sea</Place11>
		<Description>Day 01 : Meet the tour guide upon arrival. Proceed to ` Fountain Of Wealth `, Merlion Park, Little India. After                
dinner, Proceed to Night Safari ~ As the sun sets, a different world comes to life.
Day 02 : Breakfast in hotel. Check out hotel and proceed to Sentosa Island ~ Butterfly Park, Sky Tower, Underwater World.   
            End of the tour, depart to Changi International Airport.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>14</id>
		<Name>Singapore 3days 2Night Land Package A</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>Fountain of Wealth</Place2>
		<Place3>esplanade</Place3>
		<Place4>clarke quay</Place4>
		<Place5>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place5>
		<Place6>Images of Singapore</Place6>
		<Place7>Underwater World</Place7>
		<Place8>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place8>
		<Place9>Siloso Beach</Place9>
		<Place10>songs of the sea</Place10>
		<Place11>Causeway Bridge</Place11>
		<Place12>Tiger Sky Tower</Place12>
		<Place13>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place13>
		<Place14>Chinatown Night Market</Place14>
		<Place15>Trishaw</Place15>
		<Place16>Clarke Quay</Place16>
		<Place17>Bumboat River</Place17>
		<Place18>shopping little india</Place18>
		<Description>Day 01 : Meet the tour guide upon arrival. Proceed to Merlion Park, Fountain Of Wealth, Esplanade. After dinner,      
        Boat Ride in Singapore River . Check in hotel.
Day 02 : Breakfast in hotel.  proceed to Singapore Botanical Garden. After lunch, proceed to Sentosa Island ~           
      Butterfly Park, Sky Tower, Udnerwater World, Song Of The Sea.
Day 03 : Breakfast in hotel. Check out hotel and proceed to Chiantown/little India for some shopping. After lunch,           
    End of the tour. Depart to Changi Airport.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>15</id>
		<Name>Singapore 3days 2Night Land Package B</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>Fountain of Wealth</Place2>
		<Place3>Night Safari</Place3>
		<Place4>BumBoat River</Place4>
		<Place5>Images of Singapore</Place5>
		<Place6>Underwater World</Place6>
		<Place7>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place7>
		<Place8>Siloso Beach</Place8>
		<Place9>songs of the sea</Place9>
		<Place10>Causeway Bridge</Place10>
		<Place11>Tiger Sky Tower</Place11>
		<Place12>shopping little india</Place12>
		<Description>Day 01 : Meet the tour guide upon arrival. Proceed to Merlion Park, Fountain Of Wealth, After dinner, proceed to       
       Night Safari ~ As the sun sets, a different world comes to life.
Day 02 : After breakfast, Boat Ride in Singapore River. Proceed to lunch, follow to Sentosa Island ~ Underwater        
       World, Butterfly Park, Sky Tower and Song Of The Sea.
Day 03 : Visit Chinatown or Little India for last min shopping after breakfast. Finish shopping, proceed to lunch,          
     End of the tour, depart to Changi Airport.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>16</id>
		<Name>Singapore 4Days 3Nights Land Package</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>Fountain of Wealth</Place2>
		<Place3>Night Safari</Place3>
		<Place4>underwater world</Place4>
		<Place5>Butterfly_Insect_Kingdom</Place5>
		<Place6>Tiger Sky Tower</Place6>
		<Place7>Images of Singapore</Place7>
		<Place8>Underwater World</Place8>
		<Place9>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place9>
		<Place10>Siloso Beach</Place10>
		<Place11>songs of the sea</Place11>
		<Place12>Causeway Bridge</Place12>
		<Place13>shopping little india</Place13>
		<Description>Merlion Park, Fountain Of Wealth
Night Safari ~ As the sun sets, a different world comes to life.
Sentosa Island ~ Underwater World, Butterfly Park, Sky Tower and 
Song Of The Sea
Chinatown or Little India for shopping
Jurong Bird Park
Boat Ride in Singapore River</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>17</id>
		<Name>Singapore 5Days 4Nights Land Package</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Night Safari</Place1>
		<Place2>Mount Faber</Place2>
		<Place3>underwater world</Place3>
		<Place4>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place4>
		<Place5>Tiger Sky Tower</Place5>
		<Place6>Images of Singapore</Place6>
		<Place7>Siloso Beach</Place7>
		<Place8>songs of the sea</Place8>
		<Place9>Causeway Bridge</Place9>
		<Place10>shopping little india</Place10>
		<Place11>Jurong Bird Park</Place11>
		<Place12>BumBoat River</Place12>
		<Place13>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place13>
		<Description>ain Of Wealth
Night Safari ~ As the sun sets, a different world comes to life.
Mount Faber
Sentosa Island ~ Underwater World, Butterfly Park, Sky Tower and Song Of The Sea
Chinatown or Little India for shopping
Jurong Bird Park
Boat Ride in Singapore River 
Botanical Garden 
Home Sweet Home</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>18</id>
		<Name>4 Days 3 Nights Exchange and Tour Program
(Singapore School Tour program)</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>School Tour</Place1>
		<Place2>Singapore Discovery Centre</Place2>
		<Place3>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place3>
		<Place4>Chinatown Night Market</Place4>
		<Place5>Trishaw</Place5>
		<Place6>Clarke Quay</Place6>
		<Place7>Bumboat River</Place7>
		<Place8>Singapore Science Centre</Place8>
		<Place9>Little India arcade</Place9>
		<Place10>Night Safari</Place10>
		<Description>Day 01 ~ Arrival Singapore, follow by City
          Tour.
Day 02 ~ Visiting School in the morning,
           Discovery Centre, Chinatown,
           Clarke Quay.
Day 03 ~ Visiting school in the morning,
          Science Centre, Little India, Night
          Safari.
Day 04 ~ Breakfast / Lunch, depart
          Singapore.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/School.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>19</id>
		<Name>5 Days 4 Nights Exchange and Tour Program (Singapore School Tour Program)</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>School Tour</Place7>
		<Place8>Singapore Science Centre</Place8>
		<Place9>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place9>
		<Place10>Chinatown Night Market</Place10>
		<Place11>Trishaw</Place11>
		<Place12>Clarke Quay</Place12>
		<Place13>Bumboat River</Place13>
		<Place14>Singapore Discovery Centre</Place14>
		<Place15>Little India arcade</Place15>
		<Place16>Night Safari</Place16>
		<Place17>gem stone factory</Place17>
		<Place18>art retreat museum</Place18>
		<Place19>asian civilisation museum</Place19>
		<Place20>changi chapel and museum</Place20>
		<Place21>images of singapore</Place21>
		<Place22>Songs of the Sea</Place22>
		<Description>Day 01 ~ Arrival Singapore, proceed to
          City Tour.
Day 02 ~ School visiting, Science Centre,
          Chinatown, Clarke Quay.
Day 03 ~ School visiting, Discovery Centre
         , Little India, Night Safari.
Day 04 ~ Interview with Malay / Indian
          Family, Singapore Museum,
          Sentosa Inland ( Song Of The Sea )
Day 05 ~ Breakfast / Lunch, depart
          Singapore.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/School.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>20</id>
		<Name>Singapore ER233</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Singapore Discovery Centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Jurong Bird Park</Place8>
		<Place9>Sentosa</Place9>
		<Place10>Shopping in Bugis</Place10>
		<Description>&gt;&gt; Day 1 Singapore
Arrive Singapore transfer to hotel. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 02 Singapore
After breakfast depart for half-day sightseeing to Merlion Park, Discovery center followed. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 03 Singapore
After breakfast depart for Jurong Bird Park followed by Sentosa. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 04 Singapore Depart
After breakfast spend time in shopping. In the evening transfer to
Airport for your onward flight.</Description>
		<references>http://www.ercotravels.com/it20.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>21</id>
		<Name>Singapore (Star Cruises) ER235</Name>
		<Duration>6</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Singapore Discovery Centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Jurong Bird Park</Place8>
		<Place9>Sentosa</Place9>
		<Place10>Star Cruise</Place10>
		<Description>»Day 01 Singapore 
Arrive Singapore transfer to hotel. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 02 Singapore
After breakfast depart for half-day sightseeing to Merlion Park, Discovery center followed. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 03 Singapore
After breakfast depart for Jurong Bird Park followed by Sentosa. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 04 Singapore
In the evening arrive cruise centre to depart on a memorable cruise of two night and three days Star cruises Virgo.
»Day 05 Cruise
Full day on curise.
»Day 06 Singapore Depart
Morning leave cruise and transfer to airport for your onward flight.</Description>
		<references>http://www.ercotravels.com/it20.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>22</id>
		<Name>Singapore/Malaysia ER236
06 Nights/07 Days</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Night life (Orchard Road)</Place1>
		<Place2>Cricket club</Place2>
		<Place3>Parliament House</Place3>
		<Place4>Supreme court and city Hall</Place4>
		<Place5>Merlion park</Place5>
		<Place6>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place6>
		<Place7>Handicraft centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Images of Singapore</Place8>
		<Place9>Underwater World</Place9>
		<Place10>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place10>
		<Place11>Siloso Beach</Place11>
		<Place12>songs of the sea</Place12>
		<Place13>Causeway Bridge</Place13>
		<Description>»Day 01 Singapore
Arrive Singapore transfer to hotel. In evening, walk through Orchard road to see the nightlife in Singapore. Overnight stay at the hotel.
»Day 02 Singapore 
After breakfast depart for half-day city tour. Overnight stay the hotel.
»Day 03 Singapore
Full day at leisure for your own activities. Overnight stay at hotel.
»Day 04 Singapore - Kuala LumpurAfter breakfast Depart for Sentosa Island. Evening transfer to airport to connect flight for Kuala Lumpur.</Description>
		<references>http://www.ercotravels.com/it20.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>23</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>shopping little india</Place7>
		<Place8>Images of Singapore</Place8>
		<Place9>Underwater World</Place9>
		<Place10>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place10>
		<Place11>Siloso Beach</Place11>
		<Place12>songs of the sea</Place12>
		<Place13>Causeway Bridge</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird Park</Place14>
		<Place15>Night Safari</Place15>
		<Place16>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place16>
		<Place17>Chinatown Night Market</Place17>
		<Place18>Trishaw</Place18>
		<Place19>Clarke Quay</Place19>
		<Place20>Bumboat River</Place20>
		<Description>Day 06 / Delhi-Singapore
Transfer in time to airport to board the flight to Singapore.
Day 07 / Singapore
Arrive Singapore and meet assist at the airport. and transfer to hotel. Spend the rest of the day at leisure. Overnight at hotel.
Day 08 / Singapore
After breakfast proceed for a panoramic half-day city tour of Singapore visiting the parliament house Mount faber China town Raffles Street and The Westin Stamford the tallest hotel in the world. Rest of the day is free for shopping at the famous Serangoon Road. Overnight at hotel.
Day 09 / Singapore
After breakfast spend the at your own. In the evening visit the Sentosa Island or ride a cable car and visit the Wax Museum. Or take an optional visit to the fabulous light and sound show at the Musical fountains. Overnight at hotel.
Day 10 / Singapore
After breakfast visit the Jurong bird park where you can see more than 3000 species of birds. You will also get the chance to click your photographs with many lollikets perched on you. Evening proceed for a Night Safari where you can watch the mystery and drama of the jungle unfold before your eyes. Overnight at hotel.
Day 11 / Departure
After breakfast spend time on shopping. Later transfer to the Airport to board the flight for onward journey.</Description>
		<references>http://www.bookmytrip.in/packages/india-singapore.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>24</id>
		<Name>Singapore Holiday Package</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Stamford Hotel</Place8>
		<Place9>Shopping in Bugis</Place9>
		<Place10>cable car-sentosa</Place10>
		<Place11>Underwater World</Place11>
		<Place12>Merlion</Place12>
		<Place13>Causeway Bridge</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird Park</Place14>
		<Place15>Shopping Orchard</Place15>
		<Place16>shopping little india</Place16>
		<Description>Day 06: Phuket - Singapore 
After American breakfast check out of your hotel and transfer to airport to catch your flight TG 421 at 1120 Hrs for Singapore. Arrive Singapore at 1405 Hrs. Upon arrival meet our representative who would transfer you to your hotel. Evening at lesisure. Overnight at the hotel.
Day 07: At Singapore 
American breakfast at the hotel. Later depart for a half day city sight seeing tour where you would get a complete glimpse of the city and various markets. Visit Parliament House, City Hall, and Mount Faber and also view the tallest hotel of the world - "Westin Stamford". Evening at leisure. Overnight at the hotel. 
Day 08: At Singapore 
Morning American Breakfast. This day is free you to explore different shopping malls of Singapore where you can shop for wide range of products which suits to your pocket. You also have an option of visiting Sentosa Island. Here enjoy a thrilling cable car ride to the Island where you will see the light and sound show at Musical fountain. Also see the Wax Museum and take a ride on the monorail which will take you round the Island. Overnight at the hotel. 
Day 09: Singapore - Bangkok - Delhi 
After American breakfast this morning is free for some last minute shopping. Later check out of the hotel and transfer to the airport to catch your flight TG 404 at 1305 Hrs for Bangkok. Arrive Bangkok at 1420 Hrs and take the connecting flight TG 315 at 1945 Hrs. Arrive into Delhi at 2240 Hrs.</Description>
		<references>http://www.cheapairticketsindia.com/holidays-abroad/singapore-tours-travel.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>25</id>
		<Name>Dream Singapore</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Zouk</Place1>
		<Place2>Crazy Elephant</Place2>
		<Place3>Velvet Underground</Place3>
		<Place4>China Jump Bar and Grill</Place4>
		<Place5>Molly Malone’s</Place5>
		<Place6>n.y.d.c.</Place6>
		<Place7>Cricket club</Place7>
		<Place8>Parliament House</Place8>
		<Place9>Supreme court and city Hall</Place9>
		<Place10>Merlion park</Place10>
		<Place11>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place11>
		<Place12>Handicraft centre</Place12>
		<Place13>Mount Faber</Place13>
		<Place14>Underwater World</Place14>
		<Place15>Cable Car-Sentosa</Place15>
		<Place16>Images of Singapore</Place16>
		<Place17>Songs of the Sea</Place17>
		<Place18>Sentosa 4D Magix</Place18>
		<Description>Day-01
Arrival Singapore 
Arrival Singapore the most happening city of Asia on arrival beautiful changi International Airport meet our local representative and transfer to your Hotel New Park 4 star or similar type hotel rest of the day is free on your Own to explore the wonders of this vibrant city dinner at hotel restaurant and over night stay at Hotel.
Day-02 
After morning break fast proceed on a guided orientation city tour driving past famous land marks like the city hall, Parliment house, Down town, Mariyamma temple, china town, after lunch at the hotel transfer to mount Faber from where proceed to sentosa island by a panoramic Cable car ride across the harbor. Here you will visit Wax Museum discover the island by monorail ride and visit under water world end the day with the sensational '' Magical sentosa'' show at the Musical fountain. The sound light and laser extravaganza will be an experience of a life time evening return back to hotel dinner at hotel restaurant and over night stay at Hotel.
Day-0 3 
After morning breakfast at the hotel proceed to JURONG BIRD PARK see exotic birds performing exciting shows at the park transfer to the hotel rest of the day is free for shopping at orchard road . High street center, Mohammed Mustafa shopping center and dinner at hotel restaurant and over night stay at the Hotel
Day-04 
After Morning breakfast check out hotel and transfer to the International air port to board your onward flight reach home with sweet memories of Singapore</Description>
		<references>http://www.greatindiaholidays.theindiancenter.com/dream-vacation-tour.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>26</id>
		<Name>Travel From India / Singapore Package / Singapore</Name>
		<Duration>2</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>NEWater visitor centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Bumboat river</Place8>
		<Description>02 Nights Accommodatiom 
Daily Breakfast 
Airport - Hotel - Airport Transfers 
Half Day City Tour 
One complimentary lunch at hotel Oxford 
One mineral water bottle for refreshments. 
Welcome drink 
Visit to New Water Treatment Plant exclusive with GTMC only. 
30 minute boat cruise at Singapore River. 
15% discount on Hard Rock food and beverages 
S$ 05 discount voucher on purchase at Hard Rock 
All Hotel Applicable Taxes 
Guide Services.</Description>
		<references>http://www.swiftravel.com/S_package_details_intl.asp?pid=22andgid=10</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>27</id>
		<Name>UNIQUELY SINGAPORE 3 Nights - 4 Days 3 Nights</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>National Orchid Garden</Place7>
		<Place8>Shopping Orchard</Place8>
		<Place9>Tigerlive</Place9>
		<Description>Day 01 : Home Destination – Singapore 
Arrive Singapore international airport . Meeting and assistance on arrival . Seat in coach transfer to hotel . Check in hotel . Rest of day is free on leisure . Overnight stay at hotel . 
Day 2
Day 02 : Singapore 
Morning after breakfast , pick up from hotel lobby for half day city tour in seat in coach transfer . An Orientation tour of our city begins with a drive around the Civic District past the Padang, Cricket Club and the historic Parliament House, Supreme Court and City Hall. Next a stop at the Merlion Park for great views of Marina Bay and a picture-taking opportunity with The Merlion, Singapore’s well-known tourism icon, a mythological creature that is part lion and part fish. The tour continues with a visit to the Thian Hock Keng Temple, one of the oldest Buddhist-Taoist temples on the island, before driving past Chinatown to a local handicraft centre. From there we proceed to the National Orchid Garden, located within the Singapore Botanic Gardens, which boasts a sprawling display of 60,000 orchid plants comprising of 400 species and more than 2,000 hybrids. Our final stop at Little India will entrance you with the scent of joss sticks, jasmine and spices.
Return back to hotel . Overnight stay at hotel . 
Day 3
Day 03 : Singapore 
Morning after breakfast , day is free on own to explore city and market on own . In evening move for Live Tiger show on seat in coach basis . ( Live Tiger show may be arrange on day 02 depend upon service availability ) . 
Return back to hotel . Overnight stay at hotel. 
Day 4
Day 04 : Singapore – Home Destination 
Morning after breakfast , pick up from hotel . Seat in coach transfer to airport to board your flight for home back with memories.</Description>
		<references>http://www.primetravels.com/PackageDetail.aspx?PId=454</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>28</id>
		<Name>Singapore Travel Package
 3 Days / 2 Nights</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>supreme court and city hall</Place1>
		<Place2>parliament house</Place2>
		<Place3>Stamford Hotel</Place3>
		<Place4>Mount Faber</Place4>
		<Place5>cable car-sentosa</Place5>
		<Place6>Shopping little india</Place6>
		<Place7>Shopping Orchard</Place7>
		<Place8>Shopping - City Hall</Place8>
		<Description>Day 01 : Singapore
Arrive in Singapore. After immigration and custom formalities, you are met by our local representative and transferred to the hotel of your choice. The day is free for you to relax on your own. 
Overnight at the hotel 
Day 02 : Panoramic City
This morning after breakfast, we take you for a panoramic city tour of Singapore. Get a real feel of this bustling city. Enjoy a wonderful view of the city, harbour and southern island from Mount Faber, among panoramic views. Enjoy a delicious Indian lunch.
Later in the evening enjoy bargain shopping at the famous Mohammed Mustafa, Orchard road, Peninsula Plaza etc.
Overnight at the hotel 
Day 03 :
After breakfast we check out of the hotel for our flight back home. Its time to say goodbye to your friends on the tour
Hope you had a good time traveling with us</Description>
		<references>http://www.indiaetrade.com/travelling2india/singapore-travel-package.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>29</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package|Tour Package for Singapore Asia  03 Nights / 04 Days</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Sri Mariamman Temple</Place1>
		<Place2>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place2>
		<Place3>Images of Singapore</Place3>
		<Place4>Underwater World</Place4>
		<Place5>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place5>
		<Place6>Siloso Beach</Place6>
		<Place7>songs of the sea</Place7>
		<Place8>Causeway Bridge</Place8>
		<Place9>Jurong Bird Park</Place9>
		<Place10>Night Safari</Place10>
		<Description>Day 01 : Tour Package for Singapore Asia 
Arrive Singapore, Our representative will recieve you and you will be transferred to Hotel. Day free for familiarization/ orientation.Overnight stay at Hotel
Day 02
Sri Mariamman Temple - Famous Hindu temple in Singapore. 
Its site was acquired in 1823 by Narayan Pillai, a clerk of  East India Company who had accompanied Sir Stamford Raffles to Singapore. The Temple is dedicated to Sri Mariamman, a manifestation of the Great Goddess, worshipped for health and prosperity.
» Botanical Gardens - The Singapore Botanic Gardens ranks among the world's finest tropical gardens. Renowned for both its combination of untouched primary forest and specialty gardens , the lush gardens date back to 1822, when its British founders literally carved the gardens from the Malay jungle.
 » Sentosa Island - Sentosa Island is an island theme park and offers beaches, history, golf, gastronomy and a host of themed attractions, including Volcano Land, the Asian Village, the water rides of Fantasy Island, and Underwater World, one of Asia's largest tropical fish oceanariums. The more earnest visitor can visit Images of Singapore, which depicts the island's early life, local festivals and customs. The Island can be reached by cable car.
Day 03 : Jurong Bird Park Tour and Night Safari
The largest bird park in all of South East Asia, Jurong Bird Park is a refuge for more than 8000 birds of 600 different species from all over the world. Highlights include Waterfall Aviary, at 30m (98ft) the world's highest manmade waterfall, and the South East Asian Bird Aviary, where a thunderstorm is simulated every day at noon. The new Lodge on Flamingo Lake promises food not just fit for birds. Bird shows feature flamingos, macaws, hornbills and cockatoos and one of the biggest attractions is the Penguin Parade, housing more than 200 penguins of five species. An air-conditioned monorail covers the entire park. Afternoon free for shopping. Late Evening Night Safari.
Day 04 : Departure
You can do shopping. Transfer to airport and Departure.</Description>
		<references>http://www.pearlsindiatour.com/singapore-tour-package.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>30</id>
		<Name>Singapore Haw Par Villa and Round-Island Day Trip including Lunch</Name>
		<Duration>1</Duration>
		<Place1>Haw Par Villa</Place1>
		<Place2>Kranji Dam</Place2>
		<Place3>Kranji War Memorial</Place3>
		<Place4>kong meng san phor kark see temple</Place4>
		<Place5>changi chapel and museum</Place5>
		<Place6>Johore Battery</Place6>
		<Description>Take a Singapore round-island day tour to Haw Par Villa, Singapore’s Chinese mythology theme park crammed with statues of legendary figures. The full-day trip also retraces Singapore’s World War II history, with visits to Kranji Dam, Kranji War Memorial, Bright Hill Temple and Changi.
Haw Par Villa’s colorful statues and landscaped grounds are a Singapore highlight, and were formerly known as the Tiger Balm Gardens. The gardens provide a relaxing sojourn before the sobering reminders of Singapore’s experience in World War II. Kranji Dam, in Singapore’s north-west, was the first landing spot for Japanese advance boats. You’ll have clear views across the Straits of Johor to Malaysia and visit the Kranji War Memorial, the last resting place for allied soldiers who lost their lives in World War II. The memorial commemorates by name over 20,000 men and women of the forces who have no known grave.
After lunch on your round-island tour you’ll visit Singapore’s Bright Hill Temple, famous for its Chinese crematorium and well-stocked turtle pond. The final loop of your Singapore day trip brings you to Changi Chapel and Museum, with its memories of the Changi prisoner-of-war camp. You’ll pass the Johor Battery built by the British in 1939 and see a replica “Monster Gun”, one of the largest guns installed outside Great Britain during World War II. Your Singapore day tour returns to Singapore via a drive through Changi Village.</Description>
		<references>http://www.viator.com/tours/Singapore/Singapore-Haw-Par-Villa-and-Round-Island-Day-Trip-including-Lunch/d18-3695RITC</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>31</id>
		<Name>Singapore Honeymoon Tour Package 3 Nights / 4 Days</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place7>
		<Place8>National Orchid Garden</Place8>
		<Place9>Singapore Zoo</Place9>
		<Place10>Shopping Orchard</Place10>
		<Place11>Night Safari</Place11>
		<Place12>cable car-sentosa</Place12>
		<Place13>Underwater World</Place13>
		<Place14>Dolphin Lagoon</Place14>
		<Place15>Merlion</Place15>
		<Place16>Causeway Bridge</Place16>
		<Description>Day 01 : Arrive Singapore
On arrival at the Singapore international Airport meet our tour representative who will escort you to the cab. Check in hotel and relax for the rest of the day at the hotel. 
Day 02 (City tour n night safari):
Morning after breakfast drive out for the city tour of this beautiful city. Explore the culture, history and the lifestyle of Singapore. The attractive places here are Little India- the modest and the colourful area, Esplanade - Theatres on the Bay, Chinatown, Orchard Road - the famous shopping centre, The Arab Street, The Museum, The parliament house, Merlion Park where one can view the Marina Bay and the Merlion famous tourist icon which is a part of lion and part of fish, Singapore Botanical Garden - one can find nearly 250 species, the National Orchid Garden, The zoological gardens one can find the Pygmy Hippos, Polar Bears, and so on. Also spend time shopping at the famous shopping malls in Singapore
Evening drive out for the night safari is the world's first open concept of nocturnal zoo and one of the best attractions of Singapore. This zoo houses more that 700 varied animals. One can view the nearly 100 species in their natural habitat. This zoo covers 40 hectares of land and the night safari is for five hours which is covered in two stretches. One been the walking trails and the been the tram rides. One can view the barking deer, fishing cats, varied types of flying bats, leopards, Loris, owls, and so on. Later on return back to the hotel for an overnight stay. 
Day 03 (Sentosa Island Tour)
Morning after breakfast, get transferred to Mount Faber to enjoy the cable car ride to Sentosa Island. The main attraction at Sentosa Island is the sheltered beach which is of nearly 2 kms in length, the musical fountain along with the laser interaction to create the three dimensional images is one of the attractions, The dolphin show - the performance of the pink dolphins adds on to the attractions of this island, the underwater world where one can get a spectacular view of marine life and so on. Later in the night return back to the hotel for an overnight stay. 
Day 04 Singapore:
Morning after breakfast, drive to Singapore international airport to board your flight to the onwards destination.</Description>
		<references>http://slstourist.acgil.com/singapore-tour-package.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>32</id>
		<Name>Surprising Singapore 4 days</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Mount Faber</Place7>
		<Place8>Night Safari</Place8>
		<Place9>Jurong Bird Park</Place9>
		<Place10>underwater world</Place10>
		<Place11>Songs of the sea</Place11>
		<Description>Day 1 Singapore
Arrive and transfer to your hotel. 
Day 2 Singapore - City tour - Night Safari (optional) 
Breakfast. Enjoy a panoramic half-day city tour driving past the colonial buildings, government houses, Little India and Chinatown. Enjoy a panoramic view from the top of Mount Faber. Evening take an optional evening tour of the world?s only ?Night Safari?, which takes you to a remarkable 40-hectare jungle reserve where over 1200 nocturnal animals may be seen. Overnight. 
Day 3 Singapore - Jurong Bird Park (optional) - Sentosa With underwater World (Optional)
Breakfast. Morning take an optional trip to Jurong Bird Park, a beautiful landscape park housing around 3,500 birds. Enjoy the bird shows. Afternoon, you can take an optional tour to Sentosa Island, enjoy the Under-water world an exciting place where you find opportunity to enjoy marine life without getting wet, evening enjoy Musical Fountain . Overnight at hotel.
Day 4 Singapore
Breakfast. Transfer to the airport. Depart.</Description>
		<references>http://www.travelmasti.com/international/asia/singapore-tour-package.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>33</id>
		<Name>Singapore Travel Package (5 Days Singapore Tour)</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Chinatown Night Market</Place8>
		<Place9>Trishaw</Place9>
		<Place10>Clarke Quay</Place10>
		<Place11>Bumboat River</Place11>
		<Place12>Little India arcade</Place12>
		<Place13>Images of Singapore</Place13>
		<Place14>Underwater World</Place14>
		<Place15>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place15>
		<Place16>Siloso Beach</Place16>
		<Place17>songs of the sea</Place17>
		<Place18>Causeway Bridge</Place18>
		<Place19>haw par villa</Place19>
		<Description>Day 1 :
Take a walk around the Civic District. Enjoy the thrill of great shopping, and also a glimpse into the colonial past of Singapore through the architecture of the area. 
Lunch at Chijmes. Chijmes is a prominent landmark on Stamford Road. Originally an old Catholic convent school, the chapel with its glorious stained glass windows has now bee converted into a venue for special functions. It is home to a variety of specialty restaurants. 
Visit Fort Canning Park. This hill is sacred to the Malays because this is where early Malay rulers were la rest. This is also where Sir Stamford built his own bungalow. The Battle Box is the former bomb-proof World War II bunker, where Lt-Gen Percival made his decision to surrender to the invading Japanese troops. 
Head for Clarke Quay. A popular landmark by the river in Singapore. Featuring five blocks of restored warehouses, it is home to hip entertainment, dining outlets and shops of all kind including second-hand and antique shops. 
Day 2 :
Sign up for a Heartlands of New Asia - Singapore tour. Venture into the heart of Singapore with this tour, which will show you the 'where and 'how’ of every day Singaporean life. 
Visit one of our beautiful museums. Singapore has a wide range of museums like the Singapore History Museum, Singapore Philatelic Museum and Singapore Art Museum. 
read more about Singapore Art Museum
Wine and dine at Alkaff Mansion. Perched on the top of a hill with a splendid view of the sunset, this spacious colonial mansion and its sprawling landscaped gardens which belonged to a Singapore philanthropist, has been restored to its former glory and houses a notable restaurant 
Day 3 :
Have breakfast with an Orange at the Singapore Zoological Garden Take a walk through the zoo, which employs an 'open zoo concept of using mud and rock walls as natural barriers. The Singapore Zoological Gardens is considered one of the best in the world. 
read more about Singapore Zoological Garden
Visit the ethnic quarters of Chinatown, Little India and Kampong Glam. Singapore's three major racial groups - the Chinese, Malays and Indians - have the years developed little pockets of architecture, customs and colorful festival that best express their proud heritage. 
read more about Little India
Embark on a dinner cruise. Dine on a Chinese junk in the waters off Singapore and enjoy the cool sea breeze and striking skyline. 
Day 4 :
Spend the day exploring Sentosa, the island of entertainment. Visit Fort Siloso, Images of Singapore, Asian Village, Butterfly Park and Insect Kingdom Museum. 
Sign up for a Painted Faces tour. Discover the magic, meaning and precision of Chinese opera in this evening tour Learn about the different costumes and faces that are painted. 
Day 5 :
Visit Haw Par Villa Tiger Balm Gardens and Tang Dynasty and be introduced to some Chinese culture. Haw Par Villa Tiger Balm Gardens is a sprawling park based on stories from Chinese mythology. Discover the Ten Courts of Hell and enjoy the beautiful landscaping. Tang Dynasty recreates the Chinese city of Chang'An in the 7th century. 
Stroll around one of Singapore's gardens, parks and nature reserves. Known for its greenery, Singapore has numerous parks and gardens dotted around the island such as the Chinese and Japanese Gardens, Singapore Botanical Gardens, Mandai Orchid Gardens, Bukit Timah Nature Reserve and Sungei Buloh Nature Park. Alternatively, go shopping at Orchard Road. This main belt stretching from Tanglin to Dhoby Ghaut is lined with shopping malls where you can find a wealth of quality goods. 
Have dinner at the Raffles Hotel. Lovingly restored to its former glory, the Raffles Hotel is one of the great 19th century hotels in the world. Visit the Raffles Hotel museum and dine at one of it many restaurants.</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/singapore-travel-package.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>34</id>
		<Name>Singapore Vacation (4 days)</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place7>
		<Place8>Chinatown Night Market</Place8>
		<Place9>Trishaw</Place9>
		<Place10>Clarke Quay</Place10>
		<Place11>Bumboat River</Place11>
		<Place12>Sri Mariamman Temple</Place12>
		<Place13>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place13>
		<Place14>cable car-sentosa</Place14>
		<Place15>Underwater World</Place15>
		<Place16>Dolphin Lagoon</Place16>
		<Place17>Merlion</Place17>
		<Place18>Causeway Bridge</Place18>
		<Place19>Jurong Bird Park</Place19>
		<Description>Day 1 : Singapore 
Arrive Singapore, you will be met and transferred by our representative to Hotel. Day free for familiarization / orientation.
Day 2 : Singapore City Highlights 
After breakfast, City tour of Singapore covering Emperors Palace, the city centre, Chinatown, Sree Mariayamman Hindu Temple, Mount Faber, Botanical Garden, Singapore river etc. Afternoon Sentosa Island tour with Underwater world.
read more about Sentosa
City Highlights: The City Experience Tour showcases the contrast of old and new and the blend of East and West. Experience the history, culture and life-style of multi-racial Singapore, the exciting heart of New Asia-Singapore. We will visit the Colonial district where old Singapore begins and where modern Singapore was created, Little India, places of worship, China Town, Mount Faber which offers excellent views of the Singapore skyline, the harbour and offshore islands, and admire the best of Asian craftsmanship at a Gem Factory.
Sri Mariamman Temple: It is the oldest Hindu temple in Singapore. Its site was acquired in 1823 by Narayan Pillai, a clerk of the East India Company who had accompanied Sir Stamford Raffles to Singapore. Since its foundation the Temple has occupied a unique place in the life of the Hindu community in Singapore and has been gazetted as a National Monument by the Government. The Temple is dedicated to Sri Mariamman, a manifestation of the Great Goddess, worshipped for health and prosperity. Sri Mariamman is popular in Southern India where goddesses are addressed as amman ('mother'). Given the large South Indian community in Singapore, temples dedicated to the Goddess and deities popular in South India dominate the landscape. 
Botanic Gardens: The Singapore Botanic Gardens ranks among the worlds finest tropical gardens. Renowned for both its combination of untouched primary forest and specialty gardens , the lush gardens date back to 1822, when its British founders literally carved the gardens from the Malay jungle. Today, four acres of those original jungle land has been preserved in their original state. Singapore River: Great cities of the world can usually take their early beginnings to the mouth of a river; Singapore is no exception. The river became a busy waterway, the lifeline of Singapore when entrepot trade was its main enterprise. The boats that used to ply their trade between the large ships on the outer roads of the harbour and the warehouses along the Singapore river. 
Sentosa Island: Singapores holiday resort-island, can be reached by cable car from Mount Faber or WTC (World Trade Center) and by ferry from WTC or overland by the Causeway-bridge. Sentosa Island said to be in direct contrast to the freneticism of Singapore, Sentosa Island is a purpose-built island theme park and offers beaches, history, golf, gastronomy and a host of themed attractions, including Volcano Land, the Asian Village, the water rides of Fantasy Island, and Underwater World, one of Asia's largest tropical fish oceanariums. The more earnest visitor can visit Images of Singapore, which depicts the island's early life, local festivals and customs and the World War II surrender to the Japanese at Fort Silosa, which shows the bunkers and underground passages used in the island's defense. 
Day 3 : Jurong Bird Park Tour 
Jurong Bird Park tour. Afternoon free for shopping.
read more about Jurong Bird Park
Jurong Bird Park: The largest bird park in all of South East Asia, Jurong Bird Park is a refuge for more than 8000 birds of 600 different species from all over the world. Highlights include Waterfall Aviary, at 30m (98ft) the world's highest manmade waterfall, and the South East Asian Bird Aviary, where a thunderstorm is simulated every day at noon. The new Lodge on Flamingo Lake promises food not just fit for birds. Bird shows feature flamingos, macaws, hornbills and cockatoos and one of the biggest attractions is the Penguin Parade, housing more than 200 penguins of five species. An air-conditioned monorail covers the entire park. 
South East Asian Bird Aviary: This region is home to over 1,000 species of birds from a global total of 8,500 species. While the aviary has been landscaped to provide a simulated secondary rain forest environment for the birds to live in, it still gives many vantage points from which visitors can observe the birds closely, at leisure and in relative comfort. As part of the rain forest experience, there is a tropical thunderstorm that comes on at 12 noon daily. The rain falls in the centre of the aviary away from the visitors walkway. The exhibit is especially attractive for tourists from temperate countries to admire our Southeast Asian birds collection. 
Thunderstorm: 12.00 noon 
Opening Hours: 9.00 am to 6.00 pm 
Waterfall Aviary: This newly redeveloped two-hectare Waterfall Aviary remains as the worlds largest walk-in aviary with the highest man-made waterfall standing at over 30 meters. It is home for some 1,500 free-flying birds from 80 African and provides visitors with a unique opportunity to watch them roost, bathe, feed and even raise their young in their nests. Set in a valley, the Aviary is landscaped with 10,000 exotic plants comprising 125 species of trees, bamboo, palms and ground-cover vegetation to simulate a tropical rain forest. In addition, an artificial 8-m tall tree moulded from an actual 100-year-old Barking Deers Mango tree has also been planted to enhance the rainforest landscape. 
Opening hours: 9.00 am to 6.00 pm
Lory Feeding: 9.30 am, 11:30 am and 3.30 pm
Starling and Bee-eater Feeding: 10.30 am, 11.30 am and 4:00 pm 
Panorail service to Waterfall Aviary: 9.00 am to 5.30 pm
Last train service from Waterfall Aviary: 5.45 pm 
Penguin Parade: Occupying an area of 1,630 square meters, the Penguin Parade is the home to the endearing penguins found at the Bird Park. There are more than 200 of them living here. The five species on exhibit are the Humboldt, the Rockhopper, the Macaroni, the Fairy and the majestic King Penguin. 
Penguin Feeding Times: 10.30 am and 3.30 pm 
Opening Hours: 9.30 am to 6.00 pm 
Hornbills and Toucans Exhibits: Playful South American toucans tossing fruits into the air; exotic hornbills displaying their magnificent bills and casqued in flight; the female hornbill sealing herself in a tree hole for nesting these amazing and rare sights of nature are happening right here at the Hornbills and Toucans Exhibit. For visitors to the Bird Park, the sheer beauty of these birds with their colorful and magnificent bills, is a sight not to be missed. 
Hornbill Chit-Chat: 11.45 am 
The Lakes: The Parks beautiful lakes are scenic sights. A variety of water birds like swans, ducks, geese, cormorants and pelicans have made the lakes their home. Visitors can enjoy a grand view of the lakes from the Observation Pavilion, which is landscaped with bougainvillea and installed with wooden benches and electric fans.
Pelican Feeding: 9.30 am and 1.30 pm
Day 4 : Departure 
Free for shopping. Transfer to airport and Departure.</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/singapore-vacation.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>35</id>
		<Name>Isle Holiday Singapore</Name>
		<Duration>4</Duration>
		<Place1>CHIJMES</Place1>
		<Place2>Singapore Zoo</Place2>
		<Place3>bumboat River</Place3>
		<Place4>Palawan Beach</Place4>
		<Place5>siloso beach</Place5>
		<Place6>Tanjong Beach</Place6>
		<Place7>Images of Singapore</Place7>
		<Place8>Underwater World</Place8>
		<Place9>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place9>
		<Place10>Siloso Beach</Place10>
		<Place11>songs of the sea</Place11>
		<Place12>Equinox Restaurant</Place12>
		<Description>Day 1 :  
Welcome to the Lion City. Be greeted by ladies dressed in our national costumes and adorned with fresh orchid garlands. Experience a welcome dinner at CHIJMES. Be treated to a theme party set amidst 19th century gothic architecture located right in the heart of the City. Sip cocktails on beautifully manicured lawns overlooking the fountain whilst enjoying the enchanting strains of a string quartet playing throughout the everning.
Day 2 :
Morning begins at the Singapore Zoo, where an elephant waves its trunk in greeting and leads the coaches to the picnic grounds. There, a sumptuous breakfast awaits along with a charming orang-utan who joins the group. A specially arranged photography session with the animals of the wild captures this memorable morning for the incentive guests. 
Continue with a discovery tour "with a twist" where participants will get to see, feel and taste the real Singapore. 
When evening comes, enjoy the breeze on a bumboat ride on the Singapore River taking you to Boat Quay.
Experience alfresco dining by the riverside, with a wide variety of cuisine to select from. These restaurants, pubs and karaoke lounges have been restored from old warehouses. Dine and party into the wee hours of the morning.
Day 3 :
In the morning, check-in to a resort hotel at Sentosa and enjoy breakfast by the poolside before the fun in the sun. The participants are split into teams for a mini beach Olympics - a little friendly competition to spur them on. A medal for the winning team will certainly remind them of the wet 'n' wild days! Visit other highlights on the island by the monorail system. These include the Pioneers of Singapore museum, Underwater World, Fort Siloso, WonderGolf and many more. You may also be tempted to take a stroll through the nature trails or just simply enjoy the sun and the surf at any one of our pristine sandy beaches and lagoons. Cook up a feast at the sprawling fountain gardens with a barbeque dinner. A short distance away stands the magnificent 37- metre Merlion Tower which glows in the dark. Retrace the Merlion's legendary trail along the colourful Merlion walk and be teased by playful water-spouting sea creatures and carillon bells which play well-known melodies. To add to the evening's magic, a spectacular laser show staged amidst a dancing musical fountain is carefully choreographed to enchant your guests.
read more about Sentosa
Day 4 :
Awake to a hearty local buffet breakfast whilst absorbing the breathtaking views of Singapore and the harbour at the Equinox. 
A special fashion show has been arranged showcasing the latest creations of well-known local designers completes the mornings line-up. The afternoon is free for you to spend at leisure, or to shop till you drop. 
For your farewell dinner, dine at the 19th century Alkaff Mansion which sits majestically atop Telok Blangah Hill, surrounded by acres of lush landscaped greenery. An authentic Indonesian Rijstaffel (rice table) served on individual dishes by a parade of young ladies in traditional costume will certainly be an eye-opener. The evening's entertainment includes performances of traditional Malay drums which add to the evening's ambience.
After which, children waving stalks of Vanda Miss Joaquim, Singapore's national flower, will bid you goodbye. Back in your hotel rooms, your momentoes of your memorable experience are already waiting for you framed in batik photo frames. 
Singapore bids you a fond farewell and wishes to see you again soon</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/isle-holiday-singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>36</id>
		<Name>Singapore Holiday (Singapore 7 Days)</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Fort canning park</Place1>
		<Place2>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place2>
		<Place3>Katong antique house</Place3>
		<Place4>Katong-Joo chiat</Place4>
		<Place5>Peranakan museum</Place5>
		<Place6>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Chinatown Night Market</Place7>
		<Place8>Trishaw</Place8>
		<Place9>Clarke Quay</Place9>
		<Place10>Bumboat River</Place10>
		<Place11>Chinese opera shop</Place11>
		<Place12>National Museum of Singapore</Place12>
		<Place13>asian civilisation museum</Place13>
		<Place14>Jurong Bird Park</Place14>
		<Place15>Night Safari</Place15>
		<Description>Day 1 and 2 :
Leave your home country for Singapore 
Day 3 :
Upon arrival our representative will meet you and transfer you to your hotel. Balance of day at leisure.
Day 4: 
Singapore, perhaps more so than any other Southeast Asian country has attracted immigrants from all over Asia. Along with recipes from their homeland, they also bring with them distinctive architectural styles, and unique rituals and ceremonies.
Starting from the historical trail in Fort Canning, a park where early Malay royalty resided centuries ago, through a spice garden, the original site of Singapore's first Botanic Gardens, and culminating with a visit to a Peranakan family. The Peranakan's rich and lavish heritage is an eclectic mix of Malay and Chinese cultures unique to this part of the world.
Next we invite you to engage your senses in an unforgettable experience of local sights, sound and tastes at local markets. There is a potpurri of nutmeg, cardamom, incense and colorful garlands of jasmine and marigold. Fortune tellers, goldsmiths, a bustling temple, Indian pastry shops, restaurants, and traditional grocery shops selling everything from mortar and pestle to tamarind pods. Chinatown, on the other hand, is a totally different experience. Steaming hot dim sum, Chinese pottery, silk, cloisonne, joss sticks, dried mushrooms, and local fruits line the streets of Chinatown. 
Singapore offers the international shopper a wealth of choices. You will find the hottest labels from Paris and London, as well as up and coming designer labels from Singapore, and Thailand. Trendy and inexpensive clothing from Hong Kong and Indonesia along with the latest computer equipment from Taiwan may be on your shopping list. "Shop-till-you-drop" all afternoon at your leisure.
Day 5 :
Full day at leisure. In the evening, visit a Chinese opera shop run by several generations of a Teochew family that is tucked away in the corner off a major street in the city. Opera costumes and traditional headgear in brightly colored sequins and embroidery tell of heroes, great battles, and legendary times. This art form continues to be preserved at the clan association where you will find both experienced and young performers in training. Next, get behind the scenes of an opera stage where the stage is set for a great show. Observe the various intricate routines that the opera troupe goes through, from makeup and choreography, to instrumentation and costume change, and finally the opera is staged for all to see as the cymbals clash, robes flutter, and voices ring in the ancient tales. (The opera is performed on Wednesdays and Fridays only. 
Day 6 :
Full day at leisure. Discover the region's history and culture at the Singapore History Museum and the Asian Civilization Museum with our complementary tickets. There is also a host of other exceptional places to visit including the Singapore Bird Park which boasts one of the most fascinating aviaries in the region, the Night Safari, and orchid farms with some of the largest collections of orchids.
read more about Jurong Bird Park
Day 7 :
Departure transfer to the airport for your return flight to your home country.</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/singapore-holiday.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>37</id>
		<Name>Singapore Adventure Tour</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place1>
		<Place2>Chinatown Night Market</Place2>
		<Place3>Trishaw</Place3>
		<Place4>Clarke Quay</Place4>
		<Place5>Chinatown - soup restraurant &amp; herb</Place5>
		<Place6>Fort canning Park</Place6>
		<Place7>Singapore Zoo</Place7>
		<Place8>Little India arcade</Place8>
		<Description>Day 1 : 
Arrive at Changi airport in the evening where you will be met at taken directly to your hotel. Have a good nights rest before the start of tomorrow’s adventure.
Day 2 : 
Start the morning with a guided walk through the bustling, aroma filled streets of Singapore’s Chinatown. Observe unique, exotic produce and merchants hawking their ware. Learn about unusual herbs and traditional remedies when the owner of the famous Soup Restaurant will enlighten participants with his knowledge. Enjoy your first cooking demonstration of the adventure and hear about the history of the Samsui women. After your satisfying lunch Violet Oon, Singapore’s mistress of spice, will educate you on the use of select Asian herbs and spices in home cooking. For dinner you will be escorted around one of the largest open air Hawker food courts where the group will be able to eat dishes from the next day’s menu. 
Day 3 :
Begin the morning with a guided tour of the Fort Canning Spice Garden, review the herbs and spices learned yesterday and then start your day of cooking. Cover seven popular Singapore dishes including making of a rempah, or Indonesian spice paste. Relax with a late lunch and enjoy your afternoon being free and easy; try a traditional massage or chose to go for a light dinner, coffee and dessert at the Mandarin Singapore, famous for its chicken rice. 
Day 4 :
Head to the world famous Singapore Zoo for breakfast with Ah Meng, resident Orang Utan and crowd favourite. Continue on to a Soya bean factory and tour Little India with expert cook Ms. Devagi. Top this off with some spicy fish head curry served on traditional banana leaf. Afterwards go in a group to several different supermarkets, seeing the array of exotic items available. That evening will be spent dining in fine style at Doc Cheng’s after a Singapore sling at the world famous Raffles Hotel. End the night with an informative and lively talk by Peter Knipp, organiser of World Gourmet Summit.
read more about Little India
Day 5 :
Your early start will take you to a ‘wet market’ where you will see house wives and food operators gather the days supply. Stop for a light breakfast of Indian Roti Prata and Tea, then get your elbows ready for a day of Thai and Indian cooking. From Basil stir fry, to red and green curry pastes to Indian Nan and Tandoori you will be ready for a hearty lunch. The afternoon is again free and easy, or take up the massage option. If you have a penchant for sweets join the at-sunrice team and watch a chef demo on tropical pastry at the Four Season hotel.</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/singapore-adventure-tour.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>38</id>
		<Name>Singapore Trip 8 days</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>National University of Singapore</Place1>
		<Place2>Singapore Urban Redevelopment Authority</Place2>
		<Place3>school tour</Place3>
		<Place4>gem stone factory</Place4>
		<Place5>art retreat museum</Place5>
		<Place6>asian civilisation museum</Place6>
		<Place7>changi chapel and museum</Place7>
		<Place8>chinatown heritage centre</Place8>
		<Place9>images of singapore</Place9>
		<Place10>old parliament house and the elephant statue</Place10>
		<Description>Day 1 and 2 :
Depart from your home country for Singapore.
Day 3 :
Arrival in Singapore. Bus pick up and delivery. Check into the Traders Hotel Shangri-la.
Day 4 :
Morning rest, walks, etc. Afternoon orientation on Singapore and Malaysian geography, with a very brief historical overview of the region. Lunch and dinner on own. 
Day 5 :
Visit the National University of Singapore in the morning. Lecture on Singapore’s role in the global economy. Lunch in Indian restaurant in Little India. Visit Chinese and Indian ethnic communities in the afternoon. Dinner at Clark Quay with short harbor cruise.
Day 6 :
Visit the Singapore Urban Redevelopment Authority in the morning, presentation on the role of Singapore’s public housing in multi-cultural integration. Tour of Singapore and public housing projects in the afternoon. Lunch and dinner out. 
Day 7 :
Morning talk on Education in Singapore by Dr. Jason Tan Eng Thye, School of Education, National Institute of Education, Singapore (two hours). Visits to History Museum, Singapore Art Museum and the Islamic Museum. Lunch and dinner out.
read more about Singapore Art Museum
Day 8 :
Lecture on Politics in Singapore in the morning by Dr. Antonio Rappa. Visit Singapore National Parliament in the afternoon. Visit the Association of Women for Action and Research (Aware) if National Parliament visit cannot be arranged. Lunch out. Dinner and talk by Singaporean author Catherine Lim, on literature and social issues.</Description>
		<references>http://www.international-travel-tours.com/singapore-tour-packages/singapore-trips.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>39</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package</Name>
		<Duration>3</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Place7>cable car-sentosa</Place7>
		<Place8>Siloso beach</Place8>
		<Place9>Songs Of The Sea</Place9>
		<Place10>Little India arcade</Place10>
		<Place11>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place11>
		<Place12>Chinatown Night Market</Place12>
		<Place13>Trishaw</Place13>
		<Place14>Clarke Quay</Place14>
		<Place15>Bumboat River</Place15>
		<Place16>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place16>
		<Place17>Shopping Orchard</Place17>
		<Place18>Night Safari</Place18>
		<Description>To Australia, Europe, Africa, the United States and other Western countries official visits, tourism, and by Singapore Airlines (SQ) or other aviation, transit stop at Changi airport in Singapore is not anti-night or two nights, while at the same time relaxed depth understanding of Southeast Asia, the only exciting feature of the Chinese community!
Transit in Singapore, the visa-free, easy travel, Why?
Chinese citizens held by the following eight countries issued a valid visa / long-stay visa (at least one month):
Australia
Canada
Japan
New Zealand
Britain
USA
Germany
Switzerland
In return journey the way to transit in Singapore can enjoy visa-free access for 96 hours.
Three days and two nights transit tour itinerary suggestions:
First day: tour guides at the airport, city tour of Singapore scenery: like Merlion Park, Esplanade, Lin Sheng-mou national Martyrs Monument, Elizabeth Drive, via Capitol, the High Court, City Hall, Victoria theaters. Follow-up way to spend lunch Bashan, and then to the famous tourist island of Sentosa ------, cable cars, Vientiane Hall, Western music??Beach, after dinner to see "Sea Song" musical fountain. Four-star hotel
The next day: Little India, Chinatown, pull-off terminals, after lunch visit the Botanical Gardens; Singapore's most luxurious shopping streets freedom Orchard Road shopping and dinner after the world's first Night Safari, is also Singapore's most popular tourist attractions every year . Four-star hotel
The third day: Breakfast evacuation plane to fly back to the warmth of home.
Itinerary Price: RMB / person, including
1. Four / five-star hotel for 2 nights with as early as two 1;
2. 4 meals, 60 RMB / person / meal or meals characteristics;
3. Coach;
4. Drivers and tour guides;
5. Trip attractions and tickets;
According to itinerary can be adjusted length of stay, please contact our tourism experts info@jc-travel.com.sg.
I would like to advice
  Please send my itinerary details
  Please send my company referred cases
  A tourism expert, please contact me</Description>
		<references>http://www.jc-travel.com.sg/prod01.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>40</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>cable car-sentosa</Place1>
		<Place2>Underwater World</Place2>
		<Place3>Merlion</Place3>
		<Place4>Causeway Bridge</Place4>
		<Place5>Visit Bank</Place5>
		<Description>Singapore's Changi both field trip every 2.5 minutes the plane took off or landed, the world 500 strong and many Asia-Pacific headquarters of multinational companies, good infrastructure, convenient, efficient system of government and pro-business environment, low crime rate, multi-ethnic culture and the East-West cultural melting pot of various cuisines, the rich more than the nightlife and so on until a number of reasons, making here has been the first choice for business travelers in mind.
Whether you want to come to company meetings, business fact-finding mission to visit business partners, participating in exhibitions, corporate incentive travel, from booking hotels, looking for the venue, transportation, design a personalized itinerary to have to find a local secretary, accompanied by translations (multi-national language), or to find partners, understand the local business environment, looking for investment opportunities, or would like to visit the Singapore government departments or related industries trade counterparts, or other specific business requirements are welcome to contact the Division I, we have an excellent group various industries in order to provide you with consulting services.
Singapore places the first day of Beijing five-star hotels
Airport this morning after the collection, take a luxury jet to the Garden City - Singapore. Upon arrival to the hotel to rest.
Singapore places the second day of five-star hotels
After breakfast, visit the Bank (the guests make their own arrangements), after the end to the "city" outside the Taoyuan - Sentosa Island? ?appreciate the exotic scenery, the island's tourist facilities, you can enjoy playing.
Singapore places the third day of five-star hotels
After breakfast arrangements for the meeting (the arrangement of 30 conference rooms, meeting twice during the tea), arrangements for lunch and dinner.
Singapore places on the fourth day of five-star hotels
After breakfast arrangements for the meeting (the arrangement of 30 conference rooms, meeting twice during the tea), arrangements for lunch and dinner.
Singapore places the fifth day of five-star hotels
After breakfast arrangements for the meeting (the arrangement of 30 conference rooms, meeting twice during the tea), arrangements for lunch and dinner.
Singapore sixth day in Amsterdam
After breakfast rushed to the airport flight to Amsterdam.
Above as a reference tour agency is entitled to retain the seasonal / flights / visa / hotel and went to the actual situation in the country of local factors, on the trip the right to adjust the order. Guides have the right to change the itinerary depending on local conditions and dining locations, without the irresistible factors, will not be fewer trips on the scenic spots.
Division I level with a detailed itinerary and pricing, detailed itinerary and pricing please feel free to contact us.</Description>
		<references>http://www.jc-travel.com.sg/prod02.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>41</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Singapore Education Service Centre</Place1>
		<Place2>Cricket club</Place2>
		<Place3>Parliament House</Place3>
		<Place4>Supreme court and city Hall</Place4>
		<Place5>Merlion park</Place5>
		<Place6>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place6>
		<Place7>Handicraft centre</Place7>
		<Place8>school tour</Place8>
		<Place9>Images of Singapore</Place9>
		<Place10>Underwater World</Place10>
		<Place11>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place11>
		<Place12>Siloso Beach</Place12>
		<Place13>songs of the sea</Place13>
		<Place14>Causeway Bridge</Place14>
		<Place15>Little India arcade</Place15>
		<Place16>geylang serai</Place16>
		<Place17>Singapore Zoo</Place17>
		<Place18>Singapore Botanic Gardens</Place18>
		<Place19>Shopping Orchard</Place19>
		<Description>Excellent education from the beginning!
Singapore is a multi-ethnic country, with ethnic Chinese, Malay, Indian, Eurasians, and around the world work and live here a variety of ethnic people, English is the business, administrative and school education and primary language. Bilingual students to start teaching students of all ethnic unity in English teaching, at the same time also of different races to attend their mother tongue - Mandarin, Malay, Tamil. Learning English in Singapore, a unique special circumstances.
Choose to study in Singapore also selected the following points:
Outstanding point of convergence of the education system
World-class public education system
Multi-ethnic culture of the country
A variety of urban lifestyles
Safe, clean and convenient environment
Connect with the world's focal point
In recent years, more and more parents and students in the school holidays in Singapore tourism, from kindergarten to secondary school student, many also apply to English classes, parents in student learning time, specialized fieldwork government or private sector, and the scene See student apartments and other accommodation for the children to study in Singapore to prepare.
Itinerary A: 2008 Summer Tour Family Singapura (????)
Itinerary features: specifically for parents and kids tailored itinerary, in-depth understanding of Singapore's education system, a site visit the Singapore government schools, to visit local families, to understand local custom and culture, tourism as well as to pay a friend!
First day: take the luxury passenger plane arrived in Singapore's Changi International Airport, at the airport checked in the hotel after dinner;
The next day: morning, came to Singapore Education Exchange Center???to understand Singapore's education system; afternoon of urban sightseeing, Merlion Park, Esplanade, the High Court, Raffles landing points, Suntec City, Singapore National Library, clarithromycin Pier; occupancy hotel; as early as late afternoon
The third day: visit a primary or secondary, polytechnic college (secondary school) or post-secondary institutions, field visits Singapore's education environment; Singapore Town Planning Board to understand the overall planning of Singapore island and the future direction of development; Chinatown - Chinese communities and under the Nanyang Chinese ancestors immigration history; spent Pattaya Hill, Sentosa, Palawan Beach - the most beautiful man-made beach; watch after dinner, "Sea Song" laser fire and water show, returned to the hotel; as early as late afternoon;
The fourth day: Singapore visit a local family, social exchanges, and understanding of Singapore's housing environment and local customs; Little India - Learn about India Hua humanities; Malay Cultural Village; the afternoon to visit the zoo during the day - the world's most The zoo features one of 28 hectares of "open"-style garden, allowing you to get closer to nature, and a better understanding of the park more than 3600 kinds of animals and birds of the natural ecology; as early as late afternoon; occupancy hotel;
The fifth day: botanical gardens, viewing a typical tropical unique fauna; park from a total of more than 2000 kinds of tropical and subtropical perennials, as well as numerous plant breeding. In addition, there is also a primitive plant species-intensive small forests; Orchard Road duty-free shops, free shopping, the afternoon to the airport to fly back to the warmth of home, ending a happy journey; afternoon;</Description>
		<references>http://www.jc-travel.com.sg/prod03.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>42</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package</Name>
		<Duration>5</Duration>
		<Place1>Singapore Education Service Centre</Place1>
		<Place2>Merlion Park</Place2>
		<Place3>Esplanade</Place3>
		<Place4>Raffles landing sites</Place4>
		<Place5>Capitol Building</Place5>
		<Place6>supreme court and city hall</Place6>
		<Place7>statues of sir stamford raffles</Place7>
		<Place8>school tour</Place8>
		<Place9>Little India arcade</Place9>
		<Place10>geylang serai</Place10>
		<Place11>gem stone factory</Place11>
		<Place12>art retreat museum</Place12>
		<Place13>asian civilisation museum</Place13>
		<Place14>changi chapel and museum</Place14>
		<Place15>chinatown heritage centre</Place15>
		<Place16>images of singapore</Place16>
		<Place17>Singapore Zoo</Place17>
		<Place18>Night Safari</Place18>
		<Place19>Images of Singapore</Place19>
		<Place20>Underwater World</Place20>
		<Place21>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place21>
		<Place22>Siloso Beach</Place22>
		<Place23>songs of the sea</Place23>
		<Place24>Causeway Bridge</Place24>
		<Place25>Jurong Bird Park</Place25>
		<Place26>Singapore Science Centre</Place26>
		<Place27>shopping Orchard</Place27>
		<Description>Excellent education from the beginning!
Second trip: 2008 Singapore Summer Camp Xiuxue (????)
D1: Shanghai - Singapore (early, middle and late)
School collection by bus to Shanghai Pudong Airport, unified immigration and check-in, take a flight to Singapore. As early as 7:00 the next day to arrive back home to rest after breakfast. 14:00 lunch, after lunch the whole regiment car Singapore Tour appearance of the city, along the viewing Singapore's Chinatown, visit the Chinatown Heritage Center, Singapore Early History of Chinese life and business, followed by Singapore's colonial history tour - Tour Merlion Like Park, Esplanade, Raffles??shore sites, monuments, national hero Lin Sheng-mou, running through the Capitol, the High Court, City Hall, the Victoria Theater, a hundred years of suspension, Elizabeth Drive. Back home after dinner break
D2: Singapore (early, middle and late)
After breakfast in schools to carry out exchange activities, the morning of the main activities: the welcoming ceremony, welcoming remarks by the Vice-Chancellor, visited the school facilities, according to the age of Chinese students to join the corresponding arrangements??class lectures, to understand the situation in Singapore schools, lunch after the tour Little India, Malay Village, museums, night after dinner to visit Singapore Zoo, the zoo is the world's first Night Safari, a cost of Sixty million, covers an area of 40 hectares. You can enjoy a taste of the tropical rain forest at night to observe wild animals in the beautiful in life and after the return home to rest.
D3: Singapore (early, middle and late)
After breakfast in the school exchange students??, and then friendship between the two places students. After lunch, visit flowers Pattaya Hill Park, overlooking the world's largest harbor, and then to Singapore the world-famous tourist destination: Sentosa dinner dance after viewing laser water fountain, to return home after the break.
D4: Singapore (early, middle and late)
After breakfast visit Jurong Bird Park, the park has wonderful performances and birds such as penguins exhibition hall, after lunch to visit the world's advanced science centers in the world - Singapore Science Center, of which more than more than 650 interactive exhibits network, and then go to shopping strip - Orchard Road and Singapore duty-free shops, to return home to rest after dinner.
D5: Singapore - Shanghai
After breakfast aboard the aircraft to return to Shanghai, tour a successful conclusion.
We are also available in English for three days to one month's curriculum and itinerary pricing, please contact our education tourism experts.</Description>
		<references>http://www.jc-travel.com.sg/prod03.htm</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>43</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour Package</Name>
		<Duration>4 days</Duration>
		<Place1>Night Safari</Place1>
		<Place2>cable car-sentosa</Place2>
		<Place3>Underwater World</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion</Place4>
		<Place5>Causeway Bridge</Place5>
		<Place6>Cricket club</Place6>
		<Place7>Parliament House</Place7>
		<Place8>Supreme court and city Hall</Place8>
		<Place9>Merlion park</Place9>
		<Place10>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place10>
		<Place11>Handicraft centre</Place11>
		<Place12>National Orchid Garden</Place12>
		<Description>DAY 01 : 
Arrive Singapore. After Clearing Immigrations and Customs, you will be met by our representative and be transferred to Hotel. In the evening, Enjoy Night Safari Tour. Overnight at Hotel.
Interested? Contact for Details 
DAY 02: 
After breakfast at Hotel, visit Sentosa Island Tour including Underwater world, Dolphin Lagoon, Musical Fountation show, Cable car etc. Overnight at Hotel.
DAY 03:
After breakfast at Hotel, visit Half Day City Tour of Singapore coverning Padang, Cricket Club, Parliament house, City Hall, Supreme Court, Merlion Park, Thian Hock Keng temple, National Orchid Garden( entrance ticket included). Overnight at Hotel.
DAY 04:
After breakfast at Hotel, Day free at your own. We will transfer to Airport in time for your flight to Kolkata. .</Description>
		<references>http://www.new-star-tours.com/singapore/singapore.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>44</id>
		<Name>Sand and Sea</Name>
		<Duration>1 day</Duration>
		<Place1>cable car-sentosa</Place1>
		<Place2>Underwater World</Place2>
		<Place3>Dolphin Lagoon</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion</Place4>
		<Place5>Causeway Bridge</Place5>
		<Place6>Palawan Beach</Place6>
		<Place7>siloso beach</Place7>
		<Place8>Tanjong Beach</Place8>
		<Description>Stretching 3.2km long, soak up the sun along Sentosa’s sun-kissed 
beaches while engaging in various sports activities or simply chilling out 
at beachfront bars/pubs. Siloso Beach, dubbed Singapore’s Hippest 
Beach is the perfect spot for the young and restless.</Description>
		<references>http://www.celestiallinkholidays.com/sentosa.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>45</id>
		<Name>Singapore Tour
Duration: (3 Nights/4 Days)</Name>
		<Duration>4 days</Duration>
		<Place1>Night Safari</Place1>
		<Place2>supreme court and city hall</Place2>
		<Place3>parliament house</Place3>
		<Place4>Stamford Hotel</Place4>
		<Place5>Mount Faber</Place5>
		<Place6>cable car-sentosa</Place6>
		<Place7>Jurong Bird Park</Place7>
		<Place8>cable car-sentosa</Place8>
		<Place9>underwater world</Place9>
		<Place10>Dolphin Lagoon</Place10>
		<Place11>Images Of Singapore</Place11>
		<Place12>Songs Of The Sea</Place12>
		<Place13>Shopping Orchard</Place13>
		<Description>Day: 1 On to Singapore
* Visit Night Safari with dinner
Early this morning, you will proceed to Singapore, where on arrival you will be met and transferred by our local representative to your hotel (check in after 1400 hours). The rest of the day is free. Later this evening you will visit 'Night Safari', the world's first Wildlife Park build specifically for night viewing. Highlight of the visit is the opportunity to enjoy an Indian dinner at Night Safari amidst the Rain Forest.
Note: Your journey from Kuala Lumpur to Singapore, can be arranged is per your request by Air, Train or Coach.
Day: 2 In Singapore
* Guided Panoramic City Tour of Singapore
* Jurong Bird Park including lunch with the birds
* Sentosa Island with Underwater World and the sensational
    'Magical Sentosa Show at the Musical Fountain.'
Today, proceed on a 'guided panoramic city tour' driving past famous landmarks like the City Hall, Parliament House, the Tower-Like Westin Stamford Hotel and Mount Faber. Later this afternoon, visit the largest bird park in Asia Pacific, the 'Jurong Bird Park', where you will see as many as 8000 different types of birds! The highlight is a buffet lunch amidst the unique and colourful birds in the park.
Then, Proceed on an excursion starting with a panoramic cable-car ride across the harb our to 'Sentosa Island.' Visit the Wax Museum, discover the island on a monoral ride. Enjoy a visit to underwater world, Asia's most popular oceanarium. Highlight is a walk through the 83-metre-long acrylic tunnel, home to great host of creatures that inhabit the ocean depths. Enjoy the spectacular 'Magical Sentosa' show at the Musical Fountain.
Day: 3 In Singapore
* Day free for Shopping
The Day is at leisure for shopping and exploring the cosmopolitan city on your won.
Day: 4 Return home with happy memories
Today you bid farewell to your 'TYBROS Malaysia and Singapore' tour as you transfer to the airport for your flight back home. We value and welcome any suggestions you may wish to share with us. (Check out at 1200 hrs) (B Will be either in the hotel or on boar the flight)
We value and welcome any suggestions you may wish to share with us.</Description>
		<references>http://www.tybrosindia.com/malaysia-singapore-tour.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>46</id>
		<Name>City Tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
		<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
		<Place3>Supreme court and city Hall</Place3>
		<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
		<Place5>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place5>
		<Place6>Handicraft centre</Place6>
		<Description>Explore the city by driving round the Civic District, passing by Padang, the Cricket Club, the historic Parliament House, the Supreme Court and City Hall.
Next, stop at the Merlion Park and enjoy the impressive views of Marina Bay. Do not miss out on this great photo opportunity with the Merlion, a mythological creature that is part lion and part fish.
Visit Thian Hock Keng Temple, one of Singapore’s oldest Buddhist-Taoist temples, before driving past Chinatown. Stop by a local handicraft center and observe craftsmen at work up-close.
Proceed to the National Orchid Garden, located within the Singapore Botanical Gardens, which boasts a sprawling display of 60,000 orchid plants.
Our final stop at Little India will charm you with the scent of joss sticks, jasmine and spices.</Description>
		<references>http://www.city-discovery.com/singapore/tour.php?id=159</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>47</id>
		<Name>Panoramic City Tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>supreme court and city hall</Place1>
		<Place2>parliament house</Place2>
		<Place3>Stamford Hotel</Place3>
		<Place4>Mount Faber</Place4>
		<Place5>cable car-sentosa</Place5>
		<Description>Proceed on a 'guided panoramic city tour' driving past famous landmarks like the City Hall, Parliament House, the Tower-Like Westin Stamford Hotel and Mount Faber. Proceed on an excursion starting with a panoramic cable-car ride across the harb our to 'Sentosa Island.'</Description>
		<references>http://www.tybrosindia.com/malaysia-singapore-tour.html</references>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>48</id>
		<Name>colonial City tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
		<Place2>Esplanade</Place2>
		<Place3>Raffles landing sites</Place3>
		<Place4>Capitol Building</Place4>
		<Place5>supreme court and city hall</Place5>
		<Place6>statues of sir stamford raffles</Place6>
		<Description>An orientation tour of the city which begins with a
drive past the colonial heart for a view of the Padang,
Cricket Club, Parliament House, Supreme Court and
City Hall.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>49</id>
		<Name>Sentosa Beaches</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Palawan Beach</Place1>
		<Place2>siloso beach</Place2>
		<Place3>Tanjong Beach</Place3>
		<Description>Stretching 3.2km long, soak up the sun along Sentosa's sun-kissed beaches while engaging in various sports activities or simply chilling out at beachfront bars/pubs. Siloso Beach, dubbed Singapore’s Hippest Beach is the perfect spot for the young and restless.
Palawan Beach serves a platter of fun sports and activities for the whole family! With amenities easily within reach, it’s no wonder why it is called Singapore’s Happiest Family Beach! Take a stroll with your family to the Southernmost Point of Continental Asia via the suspension bridge or bring the kids to the delightful Animal &amp; Bird Encounters which is sure to entertain.
Diehard romantics will love Tanjong Beach for their unbeatable ambience and tranquility. Spend quality time with your special someone with a quiet stroll on Singapore’s Most Romantic Beach and bask in the magnificent sunset.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>50</id>
		<Name>City Night Life (City)</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Zouk</Place1>
		<Place2>Crazy Elephant</Place2>
		<Place3>Velvet Underground</Place3>
		<Place4>China Jump Bar and Grill</Place4>
		<Place5>Molly Malone's</Place5>
		<Place6>n.y.d.c.</Place6>
		<Description>Singapore City Nightlife – You may wish to take a short nap after a long day of sight seeing so you can get out there and enjoy the hotspots in Singapore. There are plenty to pick from. Take a look at the ones we have listed below for some ideas to get you started. You may also wish to contact the tourist center or your travel agent for even more suggestions. We know you’re going to have a great time enjoying the nightlife in Singapore.
Travel Guide
If you love the excitement of a high-powered club then you’ll definitely want to check out the Zouk. This is the happening place in Singapore. Get on over to check it out and you’ll be glad you did. Try the Crazy Elephant for fantastic live entertainment. You can also grab a fantastic chocolate dessert at the NYDC while you’re in Singapore.
As you can see there are plenty of great nightspots to entertain yourself at in Singapore. Be sure to get to as many as you can while you’re visiting.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>51</id>
		<Name>Peranakan's experience</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Katong antique house</Place1>
		<Place2>Katong-Joo chiat</Place2>
		<Place3>Peranakan museum</Place3>
		<Description>ritage that combines the best of the
Chinese and Malay cultures, the Peranakan culture
has produced enviable works of art in the area
of architecture, embroidery, beadwork and the
culinary arts. Join us on a colourful journey into
the history lifestyle and unique character of the
Peranakan people as you enjoy meeting the
Peranakans. Stop for a Peranakan beading
demonstration followed by lunch at Peranakan
Restaurant.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>52</id>
		<Name>Chinatown Tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place1>
		<Place2>Chinatown Night Market</Place2>
		<Place3>Trishaw</Place3>
		<Place4>Clarke Quay</Place4>
		<Place5>Bumboat River</Place5>
		<Description>the ethnic quarter of Chinatown
and visit the Chinatown Heritage Centre, which
showcases the trials and tribulations of early
immigrants in Singapore. After dinner you will get
to visit a bustling night market. Then, hop onto
a trishaw for a ride through Chinatown to Clarke
Quay. Embark on a scenic boat trip on the
Singapore River.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>53</id>
		<Name>Eastern Heartland tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>A Kampong Glam Walk</Place1>
		<Place2>geylang serai</Place2>
		<Place3>Sultan Mosque</Place3>
		<Place4>Arab Street</Place4>
		<Place5>Parliament House</Place5>
		<Place6>supreme court and city hall</Place6>
		<Place7>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place7>
		<Place8>Bumboat river</Place8>
		<Description>The tour starts with a drive to Kampong Glam –
the historical seat of Singapore’s Malay royalty. See
Sultan Mosque as well as a wealth of souvenirs along
Arab Street, which is famous for its wide range of
textiles and basketware. Next, drive through the
Colonial district for a view of Parliament House,
Supreme Court and City Hall. Then proceed to
Chinatown where you will visit the 160 years old
Thian Hock Keng Temple before heading for a
bumboat river cruise.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>54</id>
		<Name>Sunset at Sentosa</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Images of Singapore</Place1>
		<Place2>Underwater World</Place2>
		<Place3>Butterfly_insect_kingdom</Place3>
		<Place4>Siloso Beach</Place4>
		<Place5>songs of the sea</Place5>
		<Place6>Causeway Bridge</Place6>
		<Description>A scenic cable car ride takes you to Sentosa where
diverse adventures await at Images of Singapore,
Underwater World, Butterfly Park, Siloso Beach
and the spectacular Musical Fountain. Return to
the mainland via a coach ride across the Causeway
Bridge.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>55</id>
		<Name>Shopping in Bugis</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>Bugis Street</Place1>
		<Place2>Bugis Junction</Place2>
		<Description>Bugis Village
Opposite Parco Bugis Junction area
Nearest MRT station: Bugis (EW12)
Possibly one of the best known areas of Singapore, this enclave has undergone a fair amount of transformation since the days of alleyways and sailors' haunts. It is now highly urbanised and sophisticated, with restored shophouses and shopping complexes. Care has been taken to preserve hints of this area's old-world charm. Don't miss the 'pasar malam' (night market)!
Parco Bugis Junction
200 Bugis Junction
Tel: (65) 6334 8831
Nearest MRT: Bugis (EW12)
Lots of little shops selling everything from electronic items to clothes, knick-knacks and accessories can be found in this hub. Parco Bugis Junction, Singapore's first glass-covered air-conditioned shopping street boasts a delightful mix of clusters of shophouses, modern retail outlets and a sprawling Japanese department store, Seiyu. Food outlets also abound, and the complex aims to have something of interest for every member of the family - including a cineplex.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>56</id>
		<Name>Shopping Orchard</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>The Centrepoint</Place1>
		<Place2>Delfi Orchard</Place2>
		<Place3>Far East Plaza</Place3>
		<Place4>Lucky Plaza</Place4>
		<Place5>Orchard Plaza</Place5>
		<Place6>Paragon Shopping Centre</Place6>
		<Place7>Ngee Ann City</Place7>
		<Description>road to see the nightlife in Singapore. Orchard Road shopping malls of course dominate the Singapore designer brands arena and if your wallet is up to it, head there. Dive into Ferragamo, Louis Vuitton, Max Mara, Christian Dior, Gucci, Chanel and French brands with unpronounceable names. Attractive big discount Singapore summer sales feed the tourist shopping frenzy at places like Ngee Ann City, Takashimaya, Hereen, Lucky Plaza, Paragon, Tang’s (next to the Singapore Marriott), Forum (Toys R Us), Shaw House, Tanglin Mall (with the hugely popular That CD music store) and the less pinching Far East Plaza where you can choose between fast-food and tailors.
There’s a large Kinokuniya bookstore at Takashimaya but the general browsing and hangout favourite remains the huge Borders book shop (Orchard Road and Scotts Road intersection) where patrons are encouraged to open books, lounge about, and READ.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>57</id>
		<Name>Museums</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>gem stone factory</Place1>
		<Place2>art retreat museum</Place2>
		<Place3>asian civilisation museum</Place3>
		<Place4>changi chapel and museum</Place4>
		<Place5>chinatown heritage centre</Place5>
		<Place6>images of singapore</Place6>
		<Description>Learn the Singapore history, Culture and Development, Ethic.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
		<id>58</id>
		<Name>Sentosa Tour</Name>
		<Duration>0.5</Duration>
		<Place1>cable car-sentosa</Place1>
		<Place2>Underwater World</Place2>
		<Place3>Merlion</Place3>
		<Place4>Causeway Bridge</Place4>
		<Description>A scenic cable car ride to Sentosa to watch sharks
and other amazing sea creatures swim above and
beside you at the Underwater World – Asia’s
largest oceanarium. Next, visit the Merlion Tower,
where it offers a panoramic view from the top.
The tour ends with a coach ride across the
Causeway Bridge.</Description>
	</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>59</id>
			<Name>foodwalk-spicy-food</Name>
			<Place1>Joo Chiat Comple</Place1>
			<Place2>Joo Chiat Place</Place2>
			<Place3>Haig Road Estate</Place3>
			<Place4>Duman Road &amp; Koon Seng Road</Place4>
			<Place5>East Coast Road</Place5>
			<Description>Tour Day :   Thursday
	Start Time :  6.30pm
	Duration :  6 hours
	Tour Mode :  On Foot
	Costs :  S$50 per person. Group discounts available.
	Meals :
	 Included in price on sharing and sampling basis. Beverages excluded.
	Not included :  transfers to/ from airport/ hotel, porterage, tips, entrance fees to places of entertainment unless specified
	Requirements :  Minimum group size is 8 persons.
	Constraints :
	 Please make known your dietary requirements &amp; allergies. Light tropical clothing is recommended with comfortable walking shoes. Please ensure sufficient personal insurance cover during tour.
	Accessibility &amp; Fitness :  Minimum medium fitness level recommended due to brisk walking pace. Total walking distance is about 5km on flat grounds (with lots of breaks in between) but there may be some staircases during journey.</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>60</id>
			<Name>City Tour</Name>
			<Place1>Cricket club</Place1>
			<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
			<Place3>Supree court and city Hall</Place3>
			<Place4>Merlion park</Place4>
			<Place5>Marina Bay</Place5>
			<Place6>Thian Hock Keng Temple</Place6>
			<Place7>Handricraft center</Place7>
			<Place8>Nationa</Place8>
			<Description>Explore the city by driving round the Civic District, passing by Padang, the Cricket Club, the historic Parliament House, the Supreme Court and City Hall.
	
	Next, stop at the Merlion Park and enjoy the impressive views of Marina Bay. Do not miss out on thi</Description>
		</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>61</id>
			<Name>Sentosa Beaches</Name>
			<Place1>Palawan Beach</Place1>
			<Place2>siloso beach</Place2>
			<Place3>Tanjong Beach</Place3>
			<Description>Stretching 3.2km long, soak up the sun along Sentosas sun-kissed beaches while engaging in various sports activities or simply chilling out at beachfront bars/pubs. Siloso Beach, dubbed Singapores Hippest Beach is the perfect spot for the young and rest</Description>
		</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>62</id>
			<Name>City Night Life (City)</Name>
			<Place1>Zouk</Place1>
			<Place2>Crazy Elephant</Place2>
			<Place3>Velvet Underground</Place3>
			<Place4>China Jump Bar and Grill</Place4>
			<Place5>Molly Malone?s</Place5>
			<Place6>NYDC</Place6>
			<Description>Singapore City Nightlife ? You may wish to take a short nap after a long day of sight seeing so you can get out there and enjoy the hotspots in Singapore. There are plenty to pick from. Take a look at the ones we have listed below for some ideas to get yo</Description>
		</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>63</id>
			<Name>Panoramic City Tour</Name>
			<Place1>City Hall</Place1>
			<Place2>Parliament House</Place2>
			<Place3>Stamford Hotel</Place3>
			<Place4>Mount Faber</Place4>
			<Place5>Cable Car</Place5>
			<Description>Proceed on a 'guided panoramic city tour' driving past famous landmarks like the City Hall, Parliament House, the Tower-Like Westin Stamford Hotel and Mount Faber. Proceed on an excursion starting with a panoramic cable-car ride across the harb our to 'Se</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>64</id>
			<Name>Peranakan's experience</Name>
			<Place1>Katong antique house</Place1>
			<Place2>Katong-Joo chiat</Place2>
			<Place3>Peranakan museum</Place3>
			<Description>ritage that combines the best of the
	Chinese and Malay cultures, the Peranakan culture
	has produced enviable works of art in the area
	of architecture, embroidery, beadwork and the
	culinary arts. Join us on a colourful journey into
	the history lifestyle and unique character of the
	Peranakan people as you enjoy meeting the
	Peranakans. Stop for a Peranakan beading
	demonstration followed by lunch at Peranakan
	Restaurant.</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>65</id>
			<Name>Chinatown Tour</Name>
			<Place1>ChinaTown Heritage Centre</Place1>
			<Place3>Night Market</Place3>
			<Place4>Trishaw</Place4>
			<Place5>Clarke Quay</Place5>
			<Place6>Scenic Boat trip</Place6>
			<Description> the ethnic quarter of Chinatown
	and visit the Chinatown Heritage Centre, which
	showcases the trials and tribulations of early
	immigrants in Singapore. After dinner you will get
	to visit a bustling night market. Then, hop onto
	a trishaw for a ride through Chinatown to Clarke
	Quay. Embark on a scenic boat trip on the
	Singapore River.</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>66</id>
			<Name>Eastern Heartland tour</Name>
			<Place1>Kampong Glam</Place1>
			<Place2>Malay village</Place2>
			<Place3>Sultan Mosque</Place3>
			<Place4>Arab Street
	</Place4>
			<Place5>Parliament House</Place5>
			<Place6>Supreme Court</Place6>
			<Place7>City Hall</Place7>
			<Place8>Thian Hock Keng Temple
	</Place8>
			<Description>The tour starts with a drive to Kampong Glam –
	the historical seat of Singapore’s Malay royalty. See
	Sultan Mosque as well as a wealth of souvenirs along
	Arab Street, which is famous for its wide range of
	textiles and basketware. Next, drive through the
	Colonial district for a view of Parliament House,
	Supreme Court and City Hall. Then proceed to
	Chinatown where you will visit the 160 years old
	Thian Hock Keng Temple before heading for a
	bumboat river cruise.</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>67</id>
			<Name>colonial City tour</Name>
			<Place1>Merlion Park</Place1>
			<Place2>Esplanade</Place2>
			<Place3>Raffles landing sites</Place3>
			<Place4>Capitol</Place4>
			<Place5>the High Court</Place5>
			<Place6>City Hall</Place6>
			<Place7>the Victoria Theater</Place7>
			<Description>An orientation tour of the city which begins with a
	drive past the colonial heart for a view of the Padang,
	Cricket Club, Parliament House, Supreme Court and
	City Hall. </Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>68</id>
			<Name>Sunset at	Sentosa</Name>
			<Place1>Image of Singapore</Place1>
			<Place2>Underwater World</Place2>
			<Place3>Butterfly Park</Place3>
			<Place4>Siloso Beach</Place4>
			<Place5>Musical Fountain</Place5>
			<Place6>Causeway Bridge</Place6>
			<Description>A scenic cable car ride takes you to Sentosa where
	diverse adventures await at Images of Singapore,
	Underwater World, Butterfly Park, Siloso Beach
	and the spectacular Musical Fountain. Return to
	the mainland via a coach ride across the Causeway
	Bridge.</Description>
		</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>69</id>
			<Name>Shopping in Bugis</Name>
			<Place1>Bugis Village</Place1>
			<Place2>Parco Bugis Junction</Place2>
			<Description>Bugis Village
	Opposite Parco Bugis Junction area
	Nearest MRT station: Bugis (EW12)
	Possibly one of the best known areas of Singapore, this enclave has undergone a fair amount of transformation since the days of alleyways and sailors' haunts. It is now highly urbanised and sophisticated, with restored shophouses and shopping complexes. Care has been taken to preserve hints of this area's old-world charm. Don't miss the 'pasar malam' (night market)!
	Parco Bugis Junction
	200 Bugis Junction
	Tel: (65) 6334 8831
	Nearest MRT: Bugis (EW12)
	Lots of little shops selling everything from electronic items to clothes, knick-knacks and accessories can be found in this hub. Parco Bugis Junction, Singapore's first glass-covered air-conditioned shopping street boasts a delightful mix of clusters of shophouses, modern retail outlets and a sprawling Japanese department store, Seiyu. Food outlets also abound, and the complex aims to have something of interest for every member of the family - including a cineplex.</Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>70</id>
			<Name>Shopping Orchard</Name>
			<Place1>The Centrepoint</Place1>
			<Place2>Delfi Orchard</Place2>
			<Place3>Far East Plaza</Place3>
			<Place4>Lucky Plaza</Place4>
			<Place5>Orchard Plaza</Place5>
			<Place6>Paragon Shopping Centre</Place6>
			<Place8>Ngee Ann City</Place8>
			<Description> road to see the nightlife in Singapore. Orchard Road shopping malls of course dominate the Singapore designer brands arena and if your wallet is up to it, head there. Dive into Ferragamo, Louis Vuitton, Max Mara, Christian Dior, Gucci, Chanel and French brands with unpronounceable names. Attractive big discount Singapore summer sales feed the tourist shopping frenzy at places like Ngee Ann City, Takashimaya, Hereen, Lucky Plaza, Paragon, Tang’s (next to the Singapore Marriott), Forum (Toys R Us), Shaw House, Tanglin Mall (with the hugely popular That CD music store) and the less pinching Far East Plaza where you can choose between fast-food and tailors.
	
	There's a large Kinokuniya bookstore at Takashimaya but the general browsing and hangout favourite remains the huge Borders book shop (Orchard Road and Scotts Road intersection) where patrons are encouraged to open books, lounge about, and READ. </Description>
		</Package>
		<Package>
			<id>71</id>
			<Name>Museum</Name>
			<Place1>gem store factory</Place1>
			<Place2>art retreat museum</Place2>
			<Place4>asian civilisation museum</Place4>
			<Place6>changi chapel museum</Place6>
			<Place7>chinatown heritage centre</Place7>
			<Place8>images of singapore</Place8>
			<Description>Learn the Singapore history, Culture and Development, Ethic.</Description>
		</Package>
	<Package>
			<id>72</id>
			<Name>Sentosa Tour</Name>
			<Place1>Cable Car</Place1>
			<Place2>Underwater Wrold</Place2>
			<Place3>Merlion Tower</Place3>
			<Place4>Causeway Bridge</Place4>
			<Description>A scenic cable car ride to Sentosa to watch sharks
	and other amazing sea creatures swim above and
	beside you at the Underwater World - Asia's
	largest oceanarium. Next, visit the Merlion Tower,
	where it offers a panoramic view from the top.
	The tour ends with a coach ride across the
	Causeway Bridge.</Description>
	</Package>
</Packages>